<resources>
    <string name="app_name">English for IT</string>
    <string name="user">Email;</string>
    <string name="password">Password ;</string>
    <string name="name">Name ;</string>

    <string name="open">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="close">Close Drawer</string>
<!--unit1-->
    <string name="stringEndLine">\n\n\n</string>
    <string name="styleText1"><b>Hardware</b> is any electronic or mechanical part you can see or touch.</string>
    <string name="styleText2"><b>Software</b> is a set of instructions, called a program, which tells the computer what to do.</string>
    <string name="styleText3"><b>Software</b> There are three basic hardware sections: <b>the central processing unit ( CPU)</b>, <b>main memory</b> and <b>peripherals</b>. Perhaps the most influential component is the central processing unit. Its function is to program instructions and coordinate the activities of all the other units. I a way, it is the “brain off the computer. The main memory ( a collection of RAM chips) holds the instructions and data which are being processed by the CPU. Peripherals are the physical units attracted to the computer. The include storage devices and input/ output devices.</string>

    <!--unit2-->
    <string name="styleText4"><b>Direction:</b>Match the words with pictures.</string>
    <string name="styleText5"><b>The control unit</b> examines the instructions in the user’s program, in the user’s program, interprets each instruction and causes the circuits and the rest of the components-monitor disk drivers, etc-to execute the functions specified.</string>
    <string name="styleText6"><b>The arithmetic logic unit (ALU)</b>  performs mathematical calculations (+, -, etc) and logical operations (AND, OR, NOT)</string>
    <string name="styleText7"><b>The registers</b> are high-speed units of memory used to store and control data. One of the registers (the program counter, or PC) keeps track of the next instruction to be performed in the main memory. The other (the instruction register, or IR) holds the instruction that is being executed.</string>
    <string name="styleText8">The power and performance of a computer is partly determined by the speed of its processor. <b>A system clock</b> sends out signals at fixed intervals to measure and synchronize the low of data. <b>Clock speed</b> is measured in gigahertz (GHz). For example, a CPU running at 4GHz (four thousand million hertz, or cycles, per second) will enable your PC to handle the most demanding applications.</string>
    <string name="styleText9">RAM and ROM</string>
    <string name="styleText10">The programs and data which pass through the processor must be loaded into the main memory in order to be processed. Therefore, when the user runs a program, the CPU looks for it on the hard disk and transfer a copy into the <b>RAM</b> chips. RAM(random access memory) is volatile-that is, its information is lost when the computer is turned off. However, <b>ROM</b> (read only memory) is non-volatile, containing instructions and routines for the basic operations of the CPU. The <b>BIOS</b> (basic input/ output system) uses ROM to control communication with peripherals.</string>
    <string name="styleText11">RAM capacity can be expanded by adding extra chips, usually contained in small circuit boards called dual in-line memory modules <b>(DIMMs)</b>.</string>
    <string name="styleText12">Buses and cards</string>
    <string name="styleText13">The man circuit board inside your system is called the <b>motherboard</b> and contains the processor, the memory chips, expansions slots, and controllers for peripherals, connected by <b>buses</b>-electrical channels which allow devices inside the computer to communicate with each other. For example, the front side bus carries all data that passes from the CPU to other devices.</string>
    <string name="styleText14">The size of a bus, called <b>bus width</b>, determines how much data can be transmitted. It can be compared to the number of lanes on a motorway-the larger the width, the more data can travel along the bus. For example, a 64-bit bus can transmit 64 bits of data.</string>
    <string name="styleText15"><b>Expansion</b> slots allow users to install <b>expansion cards</b>, adding features like sound, memory and network capabilities.</string>
    <string name="styleText16">2. Using the Keyboard and Mouse</string>
    <string name="styleText17">2.1 What is computer keyboard?</string>
    <string name="styleText18">The keyboard is the piece of <u>computer hardware</u> used to input text, characters, and other commands into a computer or similar device. Even though the keyboard is an external <u>peripheral device</u> in a desktop system (it sits outside the main <u>computer housing</u>), or is \"virtual\" in a tablet PC, it is an essential part of the complete computer system.</string>
    <string name="styleText19">A standard keyboard</string>
    <string name="styleText20">1. Cursor control keys include arrow keys that move that insertion point up, down, right and left, and keys such as End, Home, Page Up and Page Down, which are used in word processing to move around a long document.</string>
    <string name="styleText21">2. Alphanumeric keys represent letters and numbers, as arranged on a typewriter.</string>
    <string name="styleText22">3. Function keys appear at the top of the keyboard and can be programmed to do special tasks.</string>
    <string name="styleText23">4. Dedicated keys are used to issue commands or to produce alternative character, e.g. the <i>Ctrl key</i> or the <i>Alt key.</i></string>
    <string name="styleText24">5.A numeric keypad appears to the right of the main keyboard. The <i>NumLock key</i> is used to switch from numbers to editing keys.</string>
    <string name="styleText25">2.2 What is a computer mouse?</string>
    <string name="styleText26">The computer mouse is an input device. It lets us tell the computer what we want by pressing on it. We call it a mouse because it looks like a real mouse. A component mouse is made up of three parts as follows; body, cable and buttons.</string>
    <string name="styleText27">When we look at the computer screen we see an arrow or a shape that moves with the mouse. This is the <b>CURSOR.</b> To tell the computer what to do, we first <b>POINT</b> the cursor by moving the mouse. Then when the cursor is where we want it, we press the button or <b>CLICK.</b></string>
    <string name="styleText28">3. How to scan an image?</string>
    <string name="styleText29">1. Make sure the scanner is connected to the computer.</string>
    <string name="styleText30">2. Lift the lid and put the original on the scanner glass.</string>
    <string name="styleText31">3. For high image quality, scan at 300 or higher.</string>
    <string name="styleText32">4. The scanning software will automatically do a preview.</string>
    <string name="styleText33">5. If the image is too dark or too light, you can adjust the brightness and contrast.</string>
    <string name="styleText34">6. Click \"scan\".</string>
    <string name="styleText35">7. If the scanned text, it can be \"read\" by OCR software.</string>
    <string name="styleText36">8. If you want to save the image, choose a file format JPEG is a good choice for photos.</string>
    <string name="styleText37">9. The scanned image can be manipulated using image editing software.</string>
    <string name="styleText38">10. An all-in-one printer/scanner can print, scan and copy.</string>
    <string name="styleText39">Picture A is a <b>handheld scanner.</b></string>
    <string name="styleText40">Picture B is a <b>flatbed scanner.</b></string>
    <string name="styleText41">4. Printing</string>
    <string name="styleText42">How to set up a new printer</string>
    <string name="styleText43">Here are the basic steps you’ll follow to set up almost any printer.</string>
    <string name="styleText44">Plug in the printer’s power cable and make sure it’s turned on.</string>
    <string name="styleText45">1. Plug in the printer’s power cable and make sure it’s turned on.</string>
    <string name="styleText46">2. Connect the included cable (usually a USB cable) from the printer to the computer.</string>
    <string name="styleText47"><b>Note:</b> The process will be different if you’re using a wireless printer.</string>
    <string name="styleText48">3. On your computer, locate the printer settings. If you’re using a windows computer, you’ll find these in the <b>Control Panel.</b> If you’re using a Mac, you’ll them in <b>System Preferences.</b></string>
    <string name="styleText49">4. Look for the option to Add a printer, then follow the instructions that appear.</string>
    <string name="styleText50">5. Now it\'s time to try printing something! For example, you could try printing <u>this test page.</u> After you click the link, select <b>File > Print</b> your web browser\'s menu, or simply press <b>Ctrl+P</b> on your keyboard (or <p>Command+P</p> if you\'re on a Mac).></string>
    <string name="styleText51">6. A dialog box will appear. Locate and select the new printer from the list, then click Print.</string>
    <string name="styleText52">7. The item will then be printed . But if it doesn\'t work, don’t panic! You can try using some of the solutions to common the problems below.</string>
    <string name="styleText53"><b>Solutions to common problems</b></string>
    <string name="styleText54"><b>Problem: Nothing happens when you try to print.</b> are several reasons a printer might not work, even if everything\'s connected properly. First, you\'ll want to make sure you\'ve put paper into the correct tray and there\'sno paper stuck inside the printer.</string>
    <string name="styleText55"><b>Problem: The printer has paper and nothing\'s stuck, but it still won\'t print.</b> If the solutions above don\'t work, <b>try canceling the print job</b> from the computer and trying again. Many printers also have a button you can use to restart the current job. If all else fails, try turning the printer off and on again to see if it fixes the problem.</string>
    <string name="styleText56"><b>Problem: The printer works, but the text is very light and difficult to read.</b> If this happens, it probably means your printer requires a new <b>ink cartridge</b>   to keep working. The instruction manual included with the printer should note what type of cartridge you\'ll need to buy.</string>
    <string name="styleText57">Practice</string>
    <string name="styleText58">Part 1: Read the text above and then answer these questions.</string>
    <string name="styleText59">1. What are the main parts of the CPU?</string>
    <string name="styleText60">a. Hardware and software</string>
    <string name="styleText61">b. Keyboard output devices</string>
    <string name="styleText62">c. Storage devices</string>
    <string name="styleText63">2. What does ALU stand for?</string>
    <string name="styleText64">a. Architecture Logic Unit</string>
    <string name="styleText65">b. Arithmetic Logic Unit</string>
    <string name="styleText66">c. Artificial Logic Unit</string>
    <string name="styleText67">3. What does ALU do?</string>
    <string name="styleText68">a. To store information</string>
    <string name="styleText69">b. To control data</string>
    <string name="styleText70">c. To perform mathematical calculations</string>
    <string name="styleText71">4. How much is one gigahertz?</string>
    <string name="styleText72">a. one thousand million hertz</string>
    <string name="styleText73">b. one thousand hertz</string>
    <string name="styleText74">c. one hundred hertz</string>
    <string name="styleText75">5. What type of memory is temporary?</string>
    <string name="styleText76">a. RAM</string>
    <string name="styleText77">b. ROM</string>
    <string name="styleText78">c. Cards</string>
    <string name="styleText79">6. What type of memory is permanent and includes instructions needed by the CPU?</string>
    <string name="styleText80">a. Ram</string>
    <string name="styleText81">b. ROM</string>
    <string name="styleText82">c. Cards</string>
    <string name="styleText83">7. How can RAM be increased?</string>
    <string name="styleText84">a. By adding extra system clock.</string>
    <string name="styleText85">b. By adding extra chips.</string>
    <string name="styleText86">c. By saving information in CPU</string>
    <string name="styleText87">8. What is the benefit of having expansion slots?</string>
    <string name="styleText88">a. Adding features like sound, memory and network capabilities.</string>
    <string name="styleText89">b. Adding features like</string>
    <string name="styleText90">c. </string>
    <string name="styleText91">Part 2.1: Look at the picture and fill in the blanks with the words given. (9&#45;13)</string>
    <string name="styleText92">function keys, alphanumeric keys, numeric keypad, cursor control keys, dedicated keys</string>
    <string name="styleText93">Part 2.2: Match the descriptions (1&#45;8) with the names of the keys (a&#45;h). Then find them on the keyboard. (14&#45;21)</string>
    <string name="styleText94">\ta. arrow keys \t\tb. return / enter\n\tc. Caps Lock \t\td. Shift \t\t\t\t\t\t\te. Tab\n\tf. Space bar \t\t\tg. Backspace \t\th. Ctrl</string>
    <string name="styleText95">13. A long key at the bottom of the keyboard. Each time it is pressed, it produces a blank space.</string>
    <string name="styleText96">14. It moves the cursor to the beginning of a new line. It is also used to confirm commands.</string>
    <string name="styleText97">15. It works in combination with other keys. For example, you press this key and C to copy the selected text.</string>
    <string name="styleText98">16. It removes the character to the left of the cursor or any selected text.</string>
    <string name="styleText99">17. It produces UPPER CASE characters.</string>
    <string name="styleText100">18. It produces UPPER CASE letters, but it does not effect numbers and symbols.</string>
    <string name="styleText101">19. It moves the cursor horizontally to the right for a fixed number of spaces ( in tabulations and data fields)</string>
    <string name="styleText102">20. They are used to move the cursor, as an alternative to the mouse</string>
    <string name="styleText103">Listening</string>
    <string name="styleText104">Listen and fill in the blank..</string>
    <string name="styleText105">1. To go back one space, hit the _________</string>
    <string name="styleText106">2. To change to capital letters, press the _________</string>
    <string name="styleText107">3. To change the capital letters permanently, hit the _________</string>
    <string name="styleText108">4. To insert a tabulation, press the _________</string>
    <string name="styleText109">5. To activate the “Ctrl” functions, press the _________</string>
    <string name="styleText110">6. To activate the “alt” function, hit the _________</string>
    <string name="styleText111">7. To stop the computer doing something, you can press the _________</string>
    <string name="styleText112">8. Select the text you want to remove, and hit the _________</string>
    <string name="styleText113">9. Please _________ your pass word.</string>
    <string name="styleText114">10. It took me two hours to _________</string>
    <string name="styleText115">Language Work</string>
    <string name="styleText116">Describing functions</string>
    <string name="styleText117">There are many ways of describing a devices function</string>
    <string name="styleText118">1. preposition (for) + gerund (v.ing)</string>
    <string name="styleText119">Example: The mouse is a device for controlling the cursor and selecting items on the screen.</string>
    <string name="styleText120">2. relative clause (which/ that)+ be (is / am / are ) + used to + infinitive</string>
    <string name="styleText121">Example: The mouse is a device which is used to control the cursor and select items on the screen.</string>
    <string name="styleText122">Describing functions</string>
    <string name="styleText123">Look at language work and then write a description their functions</string>
    <string name="styleText124">1. The Sony PlayStation 3 controller.</string>
    <string name="styleText125">2. Bar code reader</string>
    <string name="styleText126">3. webcam</string>
    <string name="styleText147"><b>Picture A:</b> https://precisionsecuritysystems.com/product/handheld-scanner</string>
    <string name="styleText148"><b>Picture B:</b> https://www.indiamart.com/proddetail/flatbed-scanner-19071977630.html</string>


    <!--unit3-->
    <string name="u3styleText1">Unit 3</string>
    <string name="u3styleText2">Computer Applications</string>
    <string name="u3styleText3">Objective</string>
    <string name="u3styleText4">At the end of this unit, students are able to identify the four categories of application software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText5">Warm-up</string>
    <string name="u3styleText6">Application software consists of programs designed to make users more productive and/ or assist them with personal tasks. The majors categories of application software are</string>
    <string name="u3styleText7">1.What are the four categories of application software?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText8">Application software consists of program designed to make users more productive and / or assist them with personal tasks personal tasks. The major categories of application software are business software; graphics and multimedia software; home; personal, and educational software; and communications software.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText9">Four Categories of Application Software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText10">Business</string>
    <string name="u3styleText11">Graphics and Multimedia</string>
    <string name="u3styleText12">- Word Processing</string>
    <string name="u3styleText13">- Database</string>
    <string name="u3styleText14">- Note Taking</string>
    <string name="u3styleText15">- Personal Information Manager (PIM)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText16">- Business Software for Phones</string>
    <string name="u3styleText17">- Business Software Suite</string>
    <string name="u3styleText18">- Project Management</string>
    <string name="u3styleText19">- Accounting</string>
    <string name="u3styleText20">- Document Management</string>
    <string name="u3styleText21">- Enterprise computing</string>
    <string name="u3styleText22">- Computer-Aided Design (CAD)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText23">- Desktop Publishing (for the Professional)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText24">- Paint / Image Editing (for the professional)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText25">- Photo Editing (for the Professional)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText26">- Video and Audio editing (for the Professional)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText27">- Multimedia Authoring</string>
    <string name="u3styleText28">- Web Page Authoring</string>
    <string name="u3styleText29">Home/ Personal / Educational</string>
    <string name="u3styleText30">Communications</string>
    <string name="u3styleText31">- Software Suite (for Personal Use)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText32">- Personal Finance</string>
    <string name="u3styleText33">- Legal</string>
    <string name="u3styleText34">- TaxPreparation</string>
    <string name="u3styleText35">- Desktop Publishing (for Personal Use)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText36">- Photo Editing and Photo Management (for Personal Use)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText37">- Clip Art / Image Gallery</string>
    <string name="u3styleText38">- Video and Audio Editing (for personal use)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText39">- Home Design/ landscaping</string>
    <string name="u3styleText40">- Travel and Mapping</string>
    <string name="u3styleText41">- Reference and Education</string>
    <string name="u3styleText42">- Entertainment</string>
    <string name="u3styleText43">- Web Browser</string>
    <string name="u3styleText44">- RSS Aggregator</string>
    <string name="u3styleText45">- E-mail</string>
    <string name="u3styleText46">- Blogging</string>
    <string name="u3styleText47">- Instant Messaging</string>
    <string name="u3styleText48">- Newsgroup/Message Board</string>
    <string name="u3styleText49">- Chat Room</string>
    <string name="u3styleText50">- FTP</string>
    <string name="u3styleText51">- Text, Picture, Video Messaging</string>
    <string name="u3styleText52">- ValP</string>
    <string name="u3styleText53">- Video Conferencing</string>
    <string name="u3styleText54">2. What are the seven forms through which software is available?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText55">Application software is available in a variety of forms.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText56">- <b>Packaged software</b> is mass-produced, copy-righted retail software that meets the needs of a variety of users.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText57">- <b>Custom software</b> performs functions specific to a business or industry.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText58">- <b>A web application</b> is a Web site that allows users to access and interact with software from any computer or device that is connected to the Internet.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText59">- <b>Open source software</b> is provided for use, modification, and redistribution.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText60">- <b>Shareware</b> is copy-righted software than is distributed free for a trial period.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText61">- <b>Freeware</b> is copyrighted software provided at no cost by an individual or a company that retains all rights to the software.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText62">- <b>Public-domain software</b> is free software donated for public use and has no copyright restrictions.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText63">3. What are the characteristics of a user interface?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText64">Personal computer operating system often use the concept of a desktop, which is and on-screen work area that has a graphical user interface. One way to start a program in Windows is to move the printer to the Start button on the taskbar and Click the Start button by pressing and releasing a button on the mouse. Then, click the program name on the menu or in a list. Once loaded into memory, the program is displayed in a window on the desktop.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText65">4. What are the key features of widely used business programs?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText66">Business software assists people in becoming more effective and efficient awhile performing daily business activities. Business software includes the following programs.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText67">- <b>Word processing software,</b> sometimes calleda word processor, allows users to create a document by entering text and inserting images, edit the document by making changes, and format the document by changing its appearance.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText68">- <b>Spreadsheet software</b> allows users to organize data in rows and columns, perform calculations, recalculate when data changes, and chart the data.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText69">- <b>Database software</b> allows users to create, access, and manage a database, which is a collection of data organized to allow access, retrieval, and use of that data.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText70">- <b>Presentation software</b> allows users to create a slide show that is displayed on a monitor or projection screen.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText71">- <b>Note taking software</b> enables users to enter typed text, handwritten comments, drawing, or sketches on a page and then save the page as part of a notebook.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText72">- <b>A personal information manager (PIM)</b> includes features to help users organize personal information. In addition to PIM software, a huge variety of business and other software for phones is available.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText73">- <b>A software suit</b> is a collection of individual programs available together as a unit. At a minimum, business software suites include word processing, spreadsheet, e-mail, and presentation programs.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText74">- <b>Project management software</b> allows users to plan, schedule, track, and analyze the events, resources, and costs of a project.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText75">- <b>Accounting software</b> helps companies record and report their financial transactions.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText76">- <b>Document management software</b> provides a means for sharing, distributing, and searching through documents by converting them into a format that can be viewed by any user.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText77">5. What are the key features of widely used graphics and multimedia programs?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText78">Graphics and multimedia software includes the following programs. Computer-aided design (CAD) software assists in creating engineering, architectural, and scientific designs.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText79">- <b>Desktop publishing (DTP),</b> software enables professional designers to create sophisticated documents that contain text, graphics and colors.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText80">- <b>Paints software,</b> also called illustration software, lets users draw graphical images with various on-screen tools.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText81">- <b>Image editing software</b> provides the capabilities of paint software and includes the capability to enhance and modify existing images.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText82">- <b>Professional photo editing</b> software is a type of image editing software that allows high-volume digital photo users to edit and customize digital photos.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText83">- <b>Video editing software</b> allows professionals to modify segments of a video.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText84">- <b>Audio editing software</b> lets users modify audio clips, produce studio-quality soundtracks, and add video to video clips.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText85">- <b>Multimedia authoring software</b> allows users to combine text, graphics, audio, video, and animation in interactive application.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText86">- <b>Web page authoring software</b> helps users of all skill levels create. We pages that include graphical images, video, audio, animation, and order special effects with interactive content.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText87">6. What Are the Key Features of Widely Used Home, Personal, and Educational Program?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText88">Software for home, personal, and educational use includes the following program.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText89">- <b>Personal finance software</b> is an accounting program that helps users balance their checkbooks, and evaluate financial plans.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText90">- <b>Legal software</b> assists in the preparation of legal documents.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText91">- <b>Tax preparation</b> software guides users through filing federal taxes.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText92">- <b>Personal DTP software</b> helps users create newsletters, brochures, flyers, advertisements, greeting and business cards, logos, and Web pages.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText93">- <b>Personal paint/image editing</b> software provides an easy-to-use interface with functions tailored to meet the needs of home and small business users.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText94">- <b>Personal photo editing software</b> is a type of image editing software used to edit digital photos. Photo management software helps users view, organize, sort, catalog, and share digital photos.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText95">- Application software often includes a <b>clip art/image gallery,</b> which is a collection of clip art and photos. Video and audio editing software is used to edit home movies, add music or other sounds, and share movies on the Web.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText96">- <b>Home design/landscaping software</b> assists with the design, remodeling, or improvement of a home or landscape.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText97">- <b>Travel and mapping software</b> enables users to view maps, determine route directions, and locate points of interest.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText98">- <b>Reference software</b> provides valuable and thorough information for all individuals.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText99">- <b>Educational software</b> teaches a particular skill.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText100">- <b>Entertainment software</b> includes interactive games, videos, and other programs to support hobbies or provide amusement.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText101">7. What Are the Advantages of and Ways to Access Web Applications?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText102">A Web application, or Web app, require less disk space on a computer than installed software and is less costly to upgrade. Users often interact with Web applications directly at the Web site, referred to as the host, through their Web browser. Some Web sites require that you download the software to your computer or device.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText103">8. What Are the Types of Application Software Used in Communications?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText1104">Application software for communications includes Web browsers to access and view Web pages; e-mail programs to transmit message via a network; instant messaging software for real-time exchange of messages or files; chat room software to have real-time, online typed conversations; text, picture, and video messaging software; RSS aggregator program to keep track of changes made to Web sites; blog software, or blogware, to create and maintain a blog; newsgroup/message board programs that allow online written discussion; FTP program to upload and download files on the Internet; VoIT(Internet telephony), which allows users to speak to other users over the Internet; and video conferencing software for meeting on a network.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText105">9. What Learning Aids Are Available for Application Software?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText106">To assist in the learning process, many programs offer Help features.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText107">- <b>Online Help</b> is the electronic equivalent of a user manual. Most online Help links to Web-based Help, which provides updates and more comprehensive resources. Popular in business, industry, and schools.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText108">- <b>Web-based training(WBT)</b> is a type of computer-based</string>
    <string name="u3styleText109">Practice</string>
    <string name="u3styleText110">1. What are the four categories of application?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText111">2. Fill in the table of the four categories of application software.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText112">Business Software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText113">Graphics and Multimedia software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText114">Home/ Personal / Education software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText115">Communication software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText116">3. Click T for True and F for False.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText117">1. The categories of application software are mutually exclusive.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText118">2. A dialog box is a window that provides information, presents available option, or requests a response.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText119">3. A font is a name assigned to a specific design of characters.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText120">4. A front is name assigned to a specific design of characters.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText121">5. To click a button on the screen requires moving the pointer to the button and then pressing and holding down a button on the mouse. (usually the right mouse button)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText122">True</string>
    <string name="u3styleText123">False</string>
    <string name="u3styleText124">4. Multiple ChoiceSelect the best answer.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText125">1. ………………….. Is mass-produced, copyrighted retail software that meets the needs of a wide variety of users, not just a single user of company.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText126">a. Open source software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText127">b. A Web application</string>
    <string name="u3styleText128">c. Custom software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText129">d. Packaged software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText130">2. ………………….. Is a collection individual programs available together as a unit.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText131">a. Shareware</string>
    <string name="u3styleText132">b. A software suite</string>
    <string name="u3styleText133">c. Packaged software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText134">d. Custom software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText135">3. ……………………allows a user to plan, schedule, track, and analyze the events, resources, and costs of a project.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText136">a. Document management software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText137">b. Accounting software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText138">c. Project management software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText139">d. CAD software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText140">4. ………………… software provides a means for sharing, distributing, and searching through documents by converting them into a format theatcan be viewed by any user.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText141">a. Word processing</string>
    <string name="u3styleText142">b. Document management</string>
    <string name="u3styleText143">c. Portable Document Format (PDF)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText144">d. Database</string>
    <string name="u3styleText145">5. …………………… is the electronic equivalent of a user manual.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText146">a. Online Help</string>
    <string name="u3styleText147">b. Web-based training</string>
    <string name="u3styleText148">c. E-learning</string>
    <string name="u3styleText149">d. Distance learning</string>
    <string name="u3styleText150">6. A(n)………………… is an online area where users have written discussions</string>
    <string name="u3styleText151">a. FTP Program</string>
    <string name="u3styleText152">b .Web browser</string>
    <string name="u3styleText153">c. text message</string>
    <string name="u3styleText154">d. Newsgroup/ message board</string>
    <string name="u3styleText155">7. With ……………., you can view, organize, sort, catalog, print and share digital photos.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText156">a. desktop publishing software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText157">b. clip art</string>
    <string name="u3styleText158">c. Photo management software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText159">d. Spreadsheet software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText160">8. ……………….helps home and small business users create newsletters, brochures, advertisements, postcards, greeting cards, letterhead, business cards, banners, calendars, logos, and Web pages.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText161">a. Note taking software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText162">b. Personal DTP software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText163">c. Blog ware</string>
    <string name="u3styleText164">d. A personal information manager</string>
    <string name="u3styleText165">You are going to listen how to save a file in application software. The learn how to activities step you through fundamental technology skills when using a computer. The learn how to exercises enable you to become more proficient with these skills.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText166">Listening</string>
    <string name="u3styleText167">Now listen how to save a file in application software and order each step into the right steps.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText168">When you use application software, usually you either will create a new file or modify and existing file. If you turn off your computer or lose electrical power while working on the file, the file will not be retained. In order to retain the file, you must save it.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText169">To save a new file, you must complete several tasks:</string>
    <string name="u3styleText170">Click the save button to save the file.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText171">Designate where the file should be stored. This includes indemnifying both the device (such as drive C) and the folder or library</string>
    <string name="u3styleText172">Initiate and action indicating you want to save the file, such as selecting. Save on the File menu.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText173">Specify the name of the file.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText174">Language work</string>
    <string name="u3styleText175">Structure</string>
    <string name="u3styleText176">Present Continuous Tense</string>
    <string name="u3styleText177">Affirmative sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText178">Subject + is, am,are + V.ing</string>
    <string name="u3styleText179">Interrogative Sentence (WHQuestion)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText180">What,When, Where, Why, Who, How + is, am, are + Subject + V.ing+?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText181">Interrogative Sentence (Yes/ No Question)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText182">Is, Am,Are + Subject + V.ing?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText183">Negative Sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText184">Subject + is, am, are +not + V.ing</string>
    <string name="u3styleText185">Example</string>
    <string name="u3styleText186">Affirmative sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText187">Example:I am playing computer games</string>
    <string name="u3styleText188">Interrogative sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText189">1) Wh-question sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText190">Example: What are you doing now?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText191">2) Yes/ No question</string>
    <string name="u3styleText192">Example: Are you playing computer games?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText193">Negative sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText194">Example: I’m not playing computer games.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText195">Practice</string>
    <string name="u3styleText196">Look at the picture and make four sentences</string>
    <string name="u3styleText197">Example</string>
    <string name="u3styleText198">1. Wh-question sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText199">What is Nan doing?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText200">2. Interrogative sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText201">Nan is playing computer games.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText202">3. Yes/ No question sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText203">Is Nan playing computer games?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText204">4. Negative sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText205">Nan isn’t playing computer games.</string>


</resources>
