<resources>
    <string name="app_name">English for IT</string>
    <string name="user">Email ;</string>
    <string name="password">Password ;</string>
    <string name="name">Name ;</string>

    <string name="open">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="close">Close Drawer</string>
    <string name="stringEndLine">\n\n\n</string>

    <string name="command1">Production and Wrap-Up</string>
    <string name="command2"><b>Direction:</b> Study the test again and then summarize into infographic.</string>



    <!--unit1-->
    <string name="u1styleText1">Unit 1</string>
    <string name="u1styleText2">Computer Users</string>
    <string name="u1styleText3">Objective</string>
    <string name="u1styleText4">At the end of this unit, students are able to describe the components of a computer.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText5">Warm-up</string>
    <string name="u1styleText6">1. What is a computer?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText7">A computer is an electronic device, operating under the control of instruction stored in its own memory, that can accept data, process the data according to specified rules, produce results, and store the results for the future use.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText8">2. How do you use computers in your free time?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText9">Rearrange the important by typing 1&#45;3.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText10">3. What are the components of a computer?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText11">Hint:</string>
    <string name="u1styleText12">Example: D[ ]sp[ ]ay monitor</string>
    <string name="u1styleText13">Type: Display</string>
    <string name="u1styleText14">1) I[ ]p[ ]t devices</string>
    <string name="u1styleText15">2) O[ ][ ]p[ ]t devices</string>
    <string name="u1styleText16">3) S[ ][ ]t[ ][ ] unit</string>
    <string name="u1styleText17">4) St[ ][ ][ ][ ]e devices</string>
    <string name="u1styleText18">5) Com[ ][ ]ni[ ][ ]ti[ ][ ] devices</string>
    <string name="u1styleText19">Presentation</string>
    <string name="u1styleText20">What is a computer?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText21">A computer is an electronic machine which can accept data in a certain form, process the data, and give the results of the processing in a specified format as information.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText22">First, data is fed into the computer’s memory. Then when the program is run, the computer performs a set of instructions and processes the data. Finally, we can see the results (the output) on the screen or in printed form (see Fig below)</string>
    <string name="u1styleText23">A computer system consists of two parts: hardware and software.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText24"><b>Hardware</b> is any electronic or mechanical part you can see or touch.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText25"><b>Software</b> is a set of instructions, called a program, which tells the computer what to do.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText26"><b>Software</b> There are three basic hardware sections: <b>the central processing unit ( CPU)</b>, <b>main memory</b> and <b>peripherals</b>. Perhaps the most influential component is the central processing unit. Its function is to program instructions and coordinate the activities of all the other units. I a way, it is the “brain off the computer. The main memory ( a collection of RAM chips) holds the instructions and data which are being processed by the CPU. Peripherals are the physical units attracted to the computer. The include storage devices and input/ output devices.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText27">The components of a computer</string>
    <string name="u1styleText28">are Input devices, Output devices, System unit, Storage devices and Communication devices.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText29">Input</string>
    <string name="u1styleText30">is any data and instruction entered into the memory of a computer. As shown in Figure below, people have a variety of options for entering data and instructions into a computer.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText31">Output Devices</string>
    <string name="u1styleText32">An output device is any hardware component that conveys information to one or more people. Three commonly used output devices are a printer, a monitor and speakers.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText33">A printer produces text and graphics on a physical medium such as paper. A monitor displays text, graphics, and videos on a screen. Speakers allow you to hear music, voice and other audio (sounds)</string>
    <string name="u1styleText34">System Unit</string>
    <string name="u1styleText35">The system unit is a cast that contains the electronic components of the computer that are used to process data. The circuitry of the system unit usually is part of or is connected to a circuit board called the motherboard.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText36">Two main components on the motherboard are the processor and memory: The process also called a CPU ( central processing unit) , is the electronic component that interprets and carries out the basic instructions that operate the computer. Memory consisted of electronic component, most memory keeps data and instructions temporarily, which means its contents are erased when the computer is shut off.)</string>
    <string name="u1styleText37">Storage Devices</string>
    <string name="u1styleText38">Storage holds data, instructions, and information for future use. For example, computers can store hundred or millions of customer names and address. Storage holds these items permanently.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText39">A computer keeps data, instructions, and information on storage media. Examples of storage media are USB flash drives, hard disks, optical discs, and memory cards. A storage device records (writes( and / or retrieves (reads) items to and from storage media. Drives and readers/ writers, which are ty0es of storage devices.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText40">Communication devices</string>
    <string name="u1styleText41">A communication device is a hardware component that enables a computer to sent (transmit) and receive data, instructions, and information to and from one or more computers or mobile devices. A widely used communications device is a modern.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText42">Communications occur over cables, telephone lines, cellular radio networks, satellites and other transmission media. Some transmission media such as satellites and cellular radio networks, are wireless, which means they have no physical lines or wires.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText43">1. What are the components of a computer?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText44">2. What does CPU stand for?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText45">a. Central Processing Unity</string>
    <string name="u1styleText46">b. Central Processing United</string>
    <string name="u1styleText47">c. Central Processing Unit</string>
    <string name="u1styleText48">d. Central Programming Unit</string>
    <string name="u1styleText49">Match these words (1&#45;9) with the correct meanings (a&#45;d)</string>
    <string name="u1styleText50">1. software</string>
    <string name="u1styleText51">2. peripherals</string>
    <string name="u1styleText52">3. main memory</string>
    <string name="u1styleText53">4. hard drive (also known as hard disk)</string>
    <string name="u1styleText54">5. Hardware</string>
    <string name="u1styleText55">6. Ports</string>
    <string name="u1styleText56">7. Output</string>
    <string name="u1styleText57">8. Central processing unit (CPU)</string>
    <string name="u1styleText58">3. Match the names of digital devices with the pictures.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText59">4. Read the sentences and choose true or false</string>
    <string name="u1styleText60">1. A keyboard is an output device.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText61">2. Touch screen is an input device.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText62">3. A printer is an output device.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText63">4. An external hard disk is a storage device.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText64">5. A memorycards are a storage device.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText66">True</string>
    <string name="u1styleText67">False</string>
    <string name="u1styleText68">Listening</string>
    <string name="u1styleText69">Listen and complete the table how they use computers.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText70">Play media</string>
    <string name="u1styleText71">Anda, age 8</string>
    <string name="u1styleText72">A primary school teacher</string>
    <string name="u1styleText73">A university student</string>
    <string name="u1styleText74">An artist</string>
    <string name="u1styleText75">Language work</string>
    <string name="u1styleText76">Wh-question-The simple present tense</string>
    <string name="u1styleText77">Form:</string>
    <string name="u1styleText78">Whquestion word (what, when...) + do / does + Subject (I, you, we...) + verb +others</string>
    <string name="u1styleText79">Structure: Wh-question-The simple present tense</string>
    <string name="u1styleText80">Wh word</string>
    <string name="u1styleText81">AUX</string>
    <string name="u1styleText82">Subject</string>
    <string name="u1styleText83">Verb</string>
    <string name="u1styleText84">Other</string>
    <string name="u1styleText85">Where</string>
    <string name="u1styleText86">do</string>
    <string name="u1styleText87">you</string>
    <string name="u1styleText88">go</string>
    <string name="u1styleText89">to?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText90">What</string>
    <string name="u1styleText91">does</string>
    <string name="u1styleText92">she</string>
    <string name="u1styleText93">watch</string>
    <string name="u1styleText94">on TV?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText95">When</string>
    <string name="u1styleText96">does</string>
    <string name="u1styleText97">Mike</string>
    <string name="u1styleText98">leave</string>
    <string name="u1styleText99">school?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText100">Who</string>
    <string name="u1styleText101">do</string>
    <string name="u1styleText102">you</string>
    <string name="u1styleText103">like</string>
    <string name="u1styleText104">much?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText105">Why</string>
    <string name="u1styleText106">does</string>
    <string name="u1styleText107">he</string>
    <string name="u1styleText108">say</string>
    <string name="u1styleText109">that?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText110">How</string>
    <string name="u1styleText111">do</string>
    <string name="u1styleText112">we</string>
    <string name="u1styleText113">reach</string>
    <string name="u1styleText114">him?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText115">These whquestion words areat the beginning of the sentence. After them, we use auxiary verb and subject.We don\'t use yes or no in the answer.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText116">Example Sentences:</string>
    <string name="u1styleText117">\'Where\' question asks for the place:</string>
    <string name="u1styleText118">Where does she live? &#45;&#45;> She lives in New York.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText119">Where do you meet your friends? &#45;&#45;> I meet them at the school.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText120">\'What\' question asks for information about something:</string>
    <string name="u1styleText121">What do you like eating most? &#45;&#45;> I like eating fruits most.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText122">What do you read? &#45;&#45;> I read funny books.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText123">\'When\' question asks for information about time:</string>
    <string name="u1styleText124">When do you meet your father? &#45;&#45;> I meet him at 9.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText125">When does she come home? &#45;&#45;> She comes home late.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText126">Language work: Practice</string>
    <string name="u1styleText127">Order these questions to the right form of wh-question-The present simple tense to appropriate with answers.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText128">Hint:</string>
    <string name="u1styleText129"><b>Example:</b> she come home When does ?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText130"><b>Correct:</b> When does she come home?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText131"><b>Answer:</b> She comes home late.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText132">\tyou computer your use in do How free time ?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText133"><b>Answer:</b> I usually use my computer to listen to music and watch a movie.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText134">\tplay you do How often computer game ?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText135"><b>Answer:</b> I sometimes play computer game.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText136">\tdoes What CPU for ? stand</string>
    <string name="u1styleText137"><b>Answer:</b> It stands for central processing unit.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText138">\tWhere do you use ? usually a computer</string>
    <string name="u1styleText139"><b>Answer:</b> I usually use a computer at computer center.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText140">\tdo What you ? do</string>
    <string name="u1styleText141"><b>Answer:</b> I’m a university student.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText142">Specialist Reading</string>
    <string name="u1styleText143">The ability of tiny computing devices to control complex operations has transformed the way many tasks are performed, ranging from scientific research to producing consumer products. Tiny \'computers on a chip\' are used in medical equipment, home appliances, cars and toys. Workers use handheld computing devices to collect data at a customer site, to generate forms, to control inventory, and to serve as desktop organizers.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText144">Not only is computing equipment getting smaller, it is getting more sophisticated. Computers are part of many machines and devices that once required continual human supervision and control. Today, computers in security systems result in safer environments, computers in cars improve energy efficiency, and computers in phones provide features such as call forwarding, call monitoring, and20call answering.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText145">These smart machines are designed to take over some of the basic tasks previously performed by people; by so doing, they make life a little easier and a little more pleasant.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText146">Smart cards store vital information such as health records, drivers\' licenses, bank balances, and so on. Smart phones, cars, and appliances with built in computers can be programmed to better meet individual needs. A smart house has a built-in monitoring system that can turn lights on and off, open and close windows, operate the oven, and more.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText147">With small computing devices available for performing smart tasks like cooking dinner, programming the DVD recorder, and controlling the flow of information in an organization, people are able to spend more time doing what they often do best -being creative. Computers can help people work more creatively.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText148">Multimedia systems are known for their educational and entertainment value, which we call \'edutainment\'. Multimedia combines text with sound, video, animation, and graphics, which greatly enhances the interaction between user and machine and can make information more interesting and appealing to people. Expert systems software enables</string>
    <string name="u1styleText149">computers to \'think\' like experts. Medical diagnosis expert systems, for example, can help doctors pinpoint a patient\'s illness, suggest further tests, and prescribe appropriate drugs.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText150">Connectivity enables computers and software that might otherwise be incompatible to communicate and to share resources. Now that computers are proliferating in many areas and networks are available for people to access data and communicate with others, personal computers are becoming interpersonal PCs. They have the potential to significantly improve the way we relate to each other. Many people today telecommute -that is, use their computers to stay in touch 65 with the office while they are working at home. With the proper tools, hospital staff can get a diagnosis from a medical expert hundreds or thousands of miles away. Similarly, the disabled can communicate more 70 effectively with others using computers.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText151">Distance learning and videoconferencing are concepts made possible with the use of an electronic classroom or boardroom accessible to people in remote locations. Vast databases 75 of information are currently available to users of the Internet, all of whom can send mail messages to each other. The information superhighway is designed to significantly expand this interactive connectivity so that 80 people all over the world will have free access to all these resources.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText152">People power is critical to ensuring that hardware, software, and connectivity are effectively integrated in a socially responsible 85 way. People -computer users and computer professionals -are the ones who will decide which hardware, software, and networks endure and how great an impact they will have on our lives. Ultimately people power must be exercised to ensure that computers are used not only efficiently but in a socially responsible way.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText153">A: Find the answers to these questions in the following text.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText154">1. Name some types of devices that use \'computers on a chip\'</string>
    <string name="u1styleText155">2. Which is not the use of handheld computers are mentioned in the text?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText156">a. To collect data at a customer site</string>
    <string name="u1styleText157">b. To generate forms</string>
    <string name="u1styleText158">c. To control inventory</string>
    <string name="u1styleText159">d. To control pets in the house</string>
    <string name="u1styleText160">3. What are smart cards used for?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText161">a. To store vital information</string>
    <string name="u1styleText162">b. To save money</string>
    <string name="u1styleText163">c. To write programs</string>
    <string name="u1styleText164">d. To build cars</string>
    <string name="u1styleText165">4: What are the benefits of using computers with the following item?</string>
    <string name="u1styleText166">1. Security system</string>
    <string name="u1styleText167">2. Cars</string>
    <string name="u1styleText168">3. Phones</string>
    <string name="u1styleText169">a. Call forwarding, call monitoring, and call answering</string>
    <string name="u1styleText170">b. Improve energy efficiency</string>
    <string name="u1styleText171">c. Safer environment</string>
    <string name="u1styleText172">B: Re-read the text to find the answers to these question.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText173">Edutainment \t\t\t\tMultimedia</string>
    <string name="u1styleText174">Expert system \t\t\tTelecommute</string>
    <string name="u1styleText175">Information Superhighway</string>
    <string name="u1styleText176">1. Multimedia materials with a combination of educational and entertainment context.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText177">2. A combination of text with sound, video, animation, and graphics.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText178">3. Use computer to stay in touch with the office while working at home.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText179">4. Software that enables computers to “think” like experts</string>
    <string name="u1styleText180">5. Internet system designed to provide free interactive access to vast resources for people all over the world.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText181">Choose the following statements as True or False.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText182">1. Computers in security systems result in safer environment.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText183">2 .Computers in cars improve energy efficiency</string>
    <string name="u1styleText184">3. Smart cards store vital information.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText185">4. Smart cards are able to use for turning on and off the lights,</string>
    <string name="u1styleText186">5. Multimedia combines text with sound, video, animation and graphics are called videoconferencing</string>
    <string name="u1styleText187">6. A built-in monitoring system has been used in a smart car.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText188">7. Expert systems can help doctors pinpoints a patient’s illness.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText189">8. Telecommute is using computers to stay in touch with the office while working at home.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText190">9. Telecommute can be used of an electronic classroom or boardroom accessible.</string>
    <string name="u1styleText191">10. Vast data bases can help the people in remote location</string>


    <!--unit2-->
    <string name="u2styleText1">Unit 2</string>
    <string name="u2styleText2">Computer Architecture</string>
    <string name="u2styleText3">Objective</string>
    <string name="u2styleText4">At the end of this unit, students are able to understand the architecture and operation of computer system</string>
    <string name="u2styleText5">Warm-up</string>
    <string name="u2styleText6">1. Look at the pictures and name these different types of devices. Then match the possible users below to each type. Justify your choice.</string>
    <string name="u2styleText7">1. student using a computer for entertainment with travelling.</string>
    <string name="u2styleText8">2. large company processing payroll data.</string>
    <string name="u2styleText9">3. travelling salesperson giving marketing presentations</string>
    <string name="u2styleText10">4. large scientific organization processing work on nuclear research</string>
    <string name="u2styleText11">5. businessperson keeping in touch with clients while travelling</string>
    <string name="u2styleText12">6. graphic designer</string>
    <string name="u2styleText13">7. secretary doing general office work</string>
    <string name="u2styleText14">2. Label the parts of computer</string>
    <string name="u2styleText15">Presentation</string>
    <string name="u2styleText16">1. What is inside a PC system?</string>
    <string name="u2styleText17">The nerve center of a PC is the processor, also called the CPU, or central processing unit. This is built into a single chip which executes program instructions and coordinates. The activities that take place within the computer system. The chip itself is a small piece of silicon with a complex electrical circuit called integrated circuit.</string>
    <string name="u2styleText18">The processor consists of three main parts:</string>
    <string name="styleText4"><b>Direction:</b>Match the words with pictures.</string>
    <string name="styleText5"><b>The control unit</b> examines the instructions in the user’s program, in the user’s program, interprets each instruction and causes the circuits and the rest of the components-monitor disk drivers, etc-to execute the functions specified.</string>
    <string name="styleText6"><b>The arithmetic logic unit (ALU)</b>  performs mathematical calculations (+, -, etc) and logical operations (AND, OR, NOT)</string>
    <string name="styleText7"><b>The registers</b> are high-speed units of memory used to store and control data. One of the registers (the program counter, or PC) keeps track of the next instruction to be performed in the main memory. The other (the instruction register, or IR) holds the instruction that is being executed.</string>
    <string name="styleText8">The power and performance of a computer is partly determined by the speed of its processor. <b>A system clock</b> sends out signals at fixed intervals to measure and synchronize the low of data. <b>Clock speed</b> is measured in gigahertz (GHz). For example, a CPU running at 4GHz (four thousand million hertz, or cycles, per second) will enable your PC to handle the most demanding applications.</string>
    <string name="styleText9">RAM and ROM</string>
    <string name="styleText10">The programs and data which pass through the processor must be loaded into the main memory in order to be processed. Therefore, when the user runs a program, the CPU looks for it on the hard disk and transfer a copy into the <b>RAM</b> chips. RAM(random access memory) is volatile-that is, its information is lost when the computer is turned off. However, <b>ROM</b> (read only memory) is non-volatile, containing instructions and routines for the basic operations of the CPU. The <b>BIOS</b> (basic input/ output system) uses ROM to control communication with peripherals.</string>
    <string name="styleText11">RAM capacity can be expanded by adding extra chips, usually contained in small circuit boards called dual in-line memory modules <b>(DIMMs)</b>.</string>
    <string name="styleText12">Buses and cards</string>
    <string name="styleText13">The man circuit board inside your system is called the <b>motherboard</b> and contains the processor, the memory chips, expansions slots, and controllers for peripherals, connected by <b>buses</b>-electrical channels which allow devices inside the computer to communicate with each other. For example, the front side bus carries all data that passes from the CPU to other devices.</string>
    <string name="styleText14">The size of a bus, called <b>bus width</b>, determines how much data can be transmitted. It can be compared to the number of lanes on a motorway-the larger the width, the more data can travel along the bus. For example, a 64-bit bus can transmit 64 bits of data.</string>
    <string name="styleText15"><b>Expansion</b> slots allow users to install <b>expansion cards</b>, adding features like sound, memory and network capabilities.</string>
    <string name="styleText16">2. Using the Keyboard and Mouse</string>
    <string name="styleText17">2.1 What is computer keyboard?</string>
    <string name="styleText18">The keyboard is the piece of <u>computer hardware</u> used to input text, characters, and other commands into a computer or similar device. Even though the keyboard is an external <u>peripheral device</u> in a desktop system (it sits outside the main <u>computer housing</u>), or is \"virtual\" in a tablet PC, it is an essential part of the complete computer system.</string>
    <string name="styleText19">A standard keyboard</string>
    <string name="styleText20">1. Cursor control keys include arrow keys that move that insertion point up, down, right and left, and keys such as End, Home, Page Up and Page Down, which are used in word processing to move around a long document.</string>
    <string name="styleText21">2. Alphanumeric keys represent letters and numbers, as arranged on a typewriter.</string>
    <string name="styleText22">3. Function keys appear at the top of the keyboard and can be programmed to do special tasks.</string>
    <string name="styleText23">4. Dedicated keys are used to issue commands or to produce alternative character, e.g. the <i>Ctrl key</i> or the <i>Alt key.</i></string>
    <string name="styleText24">5.A numeric keypad appears to the right of the main keyboard. The <i>NumLock key</i> is used to switch from numbers to editing keys.</string>
    <string name="styleText25">2.2 What is a computer mouse?</string>
    <string name="styleText26">The computer mouse is an input device. It lets us tell the computer what we want by pressing on it. We call it a mouse because it looks like a real mouse. A component mouse is made up of three parts as follows; body, cable and buttons.</string>
    <string name="styleText27">When we look at the computer screen we see an arrow or a shape that moves with the mouse. This is the <b>CURSOR.</b> To tell the computer what to do, we first <b>POINT</b> the cursor by moving the mouse. Then when the cursor is where we want it, we press the button or <b>CLICK.</b></string>
    <string name="styleText28">3. How to scan an image?</string>
    <string name="styleText29">1. Make sure the scanner is connected to the computer.</string>
    <string name="styleText30">2. Lift the lid and put the original on the scanner glass.</string>
    <string name="styleText31">3. For high image quality, scan at 300 or higher.</string>
    <string name="styleText32">4. The scanning software will automatically do a preview.</string>
    <string name="styleText33">5. If the image is too dark or too light, you can adjust the brightness and contrast.</string>
    <string name="styleText34">6. Click \"scan\".</string>
    <string name="styleText35">7. If the scanned text, it can be \"read\" by OCR software.</string>
    <string name="styleText36">8. If you want to save the image, choose a file format JPEG is a good choice for photos.</string>
    <string name="styleText37">9. The scanned image can be manipulated using image editing software.</string>
    <string name="styleText38">10. An all-in-one printer/scanner can print, scan and copy.</string>
    <string name="styleText39">Picture A is a <b>handheld scanner.</b></string>
    <string name="styleText40">Picture B is a <b>flatbed scanner.</b></string>
    <string name="styleText40a"><b>Picture A:</b> https://precisionsecuritysystems.com/product/handheld-scanner</string>
    <string name="styleText40b"><b>Picture B:</b> https://www.indiamart.com/proddetail/flatbed-scanner-19071977630.html</string>
    <string name="styleText41">4. Printing</string>
    <string name="styleText42">How to set up a new printer</string>
    <string name="styleText43">Here are the basic steps you’ll follow to set up almost any printer.</string>
    <string name="styleText44">Plug in the printer’s power cable and make sure it’s turned on.</string>
    <string name="styleText45">1. Plug in the printer’s power cable and make sure it’s turned on.</string>
    <string name="styleText46">2. Connect the included cable (usually a USB cable) from the printer to the computer.</string>
    <string name="styleText47"><b>Note:</b> The process will be different if you’re using a wireless printer.</string>
    <string name="styleText48">3. On your computer, locate the printer settings. If you’re using a windows computer, you’ll find these in the <b>Control Panel.</b> If you’re using a Mac, you’ll them in <b>System Preferences.</b></string>
    <string name="styleText49">4. Look for the option to Add a printer, then follow the instructions that appear.</string>
    <string name="styleText50">5. Now it\'s time to try printing something! For example, you could try printing <u>this test page.</u> After you click the link, select <b>File > Print</b> your web browser\'s menu, or simply press <b>Ctrl+P</b> on your keyboard (or <p>Command+P</p> if you\'re on a Mac).></string>
    <string name="styleText51">6. A dialog box will appear. Locate and select the new printer from the list, then click Print.</string>
    <string name="styleText52">7. The item will then be printed . But if it doesn\'t work, don’t panic! You can try using some of the solutions to common the problems below.</string>
    <string name="styleText53"><b>Solutions to common problems</b></string>
    <string name="styleText54"><b>Problem: Nothing happens when you try to print.</b> are several reasons a printer might not work, even if everything\'s connected properly. First, you\'ll want to make sure you\'ve put paper into the correct tray and there\'sno paper stuck inside the printer.</string>
    <string name="styleText55"><b>Problem: The printer has paper and nothing\'s stuck, but it still won\'t print.</b> If the solutions above don\'t work, <b>try canceling the print job</b> from the computer and trying again. Many printers also have a button you can use to restart the current job. If all else fails, try turning the printer off and on again to see if it fixes the problem.</string>
    <string name="styleText56"><b>Problem: The printer works, but the text is very light and difficult to read.</b> If this happens, it probably means your printer requires a new <b>ink cartridge</b>   to keep working. The instruction manual included with the printer should note what type of cartridge you\'ll need to buy.</string>
    <string name="styleText57">Practice</string>
    <string name="styleText58">Part 1: Read the text above and then answer these questions.</string>
    <string name="styleText59">1. What are the main parts of the CPU?</string>
    <string name="styleText60">a. Hardware and software</string>
    <string name="styleText61">b. Keyboard output devices</string>
    <string name="styleText62">c. Storage devices</string>
    <string name="styleText63">2. What does ALU stand for?</string>
    <string name="styleText64">a. Architecture Logic Unit</string>
    <string name="styleText65">b. Arithmetic Logic Unit</string>
    <string name="styleText66">c. Artificial Logic Unit</string>
    <string name="styleText67">3. What does ALU do?</string>
    <string name="styleText68">a. To store information</string>
    <string name="styleText69">b. To control data</string>
    <string name="styleText70">c. To perform mathematical calculations</string>
    <string name="styleText71">4. How much is one gigahertz?</string>
    <string name="styleText72">a. one thousand million hertz</string>
    <string name="styleText73">b. one thousand hertz</string>
    <string name="styleText74">c. one hundred hertz</string>
    <string name="styleText75">5. What type of memory is temporary?</string>
    <string name="styleText76">a. RAM</string>
    <string name="styleText77">b. ROM</string>
    <string name="styleText78">c. Cards</string>
    <string name="styleText79">6. What type of memory is permanent and includes instructions needed by the CPU?</string>
    <string name="styleText80">a. Ram</string>
    <string name="styleText81">b. ROM</string>
    <string name="styleText82">c. Cards</string>
    <string name="styleText83">7. How can RAM be increased?</string>
    <string name="styleText84">a. By adding extra system clock.</string>
    <string name="styleText85">b. By adding extra chips.</string>
    <string name="styleText86">c. By saving information in CPU</string>
    <string name="styleText87">8. What is the benefit of having expansion slots?</string>
    <string name="styleText88">a. Adding features like sound, memory and network capabilities.</string>
    <string name="styleText89">b. They allow data that passes from the CPU to other devices.</string>
    <string name="styleText90">c. They are high-speed units of memory used to store and control data.</string>
    <string name="styleText91">Part 2.1: Look at the picture and fill in the blanks with the words given. (9&#45;13)</string>
    <string name="styleText91a">\tfunction keys \t\t\t\t\talphanumeric keys \n\tnumeric keypad \t\t\tcursor control keys \n\tdedicated keys</string>
    <string name="styleText92">function keys, alphanumeric keys, numeric keypad, cursor control keys, dedicated keys</string>
    <string name="styleText93">Part 2.2: Match the descriptions (1&#45;8) with the names of the keys (a&#45;h). Then find them on the keyboard. (14&#45;21)</string>
    <string name="styleText94">\ta. arrow keys \t\tb. return / enter\n\tc. Caps Lock \t\td. Shift \t\t\t\t\t\t\te. Tab\n\tf. Space bar \t\t\tg. Backspace \t\th. Ctrl</string>
    <string name="styleText95">13. A long key at the bottom of the keyboard. Each time it is pressed, it produces a blank space.</string>
    <string name="styleText96">14. It moves the cursor to the beginning of a new line. It is also used to confirm commands.</string>
    <string name="styleText97">15. It works in combination with other keys. For example, you press this key and C to copy the selected text.</string>
    <string name="styleText98">16. It removes the character to the left of the cursor or any selected text.</string>
    <string name="styleText99">17. It produces UPPER CASE characters.</string>
    <string name="styleText100">18. It produces UPPER CASE letters, but it does not effect numbers and symbols.</string>
    <string name="styleText101">19. It moves the cursor horizontally to the right for a fixed number of spaces ( in tabulations and data fields)</string>
    <string name="styleText102">20. They are used to move the cursor, as an alternative to the mouse</string>
    <string name="styleText103">Listening</string>
    <string name="styleText104">Listen and fill in the blank..</string>
    <string name="styleText104a">Play media</string>
    <string name="styleText105">1. To go back one space, hit the …………………</string>
    <string name="styleText106">2. To change to capital letters, press the …………………</string>
    <string name="styleText107">3. To change the capital letters permanently, hit the …………………</string>
    <string name="styleText108">4. To insert a tabulation, press the …………………</string>
    <string name="styleText109">5. To activate the “Ctrl” functions, press the …………………</string>
    <string name="styleText110">6. To activate the “alt” function, hit the …………………</string>
    <string name="styleText111">7. To stop the computer doing something, you can press the …………………</string>
    <string name="styleText112">8. Select the text you want to remove, and hit the …………………</string>
    <string name="styleText113">9. Please ………………… your pass word.</string>
    <string name="styleText114">10. It took me two hours to …………………</string>
    <string name="styleText115">Language Work</string>
    <string name="styleText116">Describing functions</string>
    <string name="styleText117">There are many ways of describing a devices function</string>
    <string name="styleText118"><b>1. preposition (for) + gerund (v.ing)</b></string>
    <string name="styleText119"><b>Example:</b> The mouse is a device for controlling the cursor and selecting items on the screen.</string>
    <string name="styleText120"><b>2. relative clause (which/ that)+ be (is / am / are ) + used to + infinitive</b></string>
    <string name="styleText121"><b>Example:</b> The mouse is a device which is used to control the cursor and select items on the screen.</string>
    <string name="styleText122">Describing functions</string>
    <string name="styleText123">Look at language work and then write a description their functions</string>
    <string name="styleText124">1. The Sony PlayStation 3 controller.</string>
    <string name="styleText125">2. Bar code reader</string>
    <string name="styleText126">3. webcam</string>

    <!--unit3-->
    <string name="u3styleText1">Unit 3</string>
    <string name="u3styleText2">Computer Applications</string>
    <string name="u3styleText3">Objective</string>
    <string name="u3styleText4">At the end of this unit, students are able to identify the four categories of application software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText5">Warm-up</string>
    <string name="u3styleText6">Application software consists of programs designed to make users more productive and/ or assist them with personal tasks. The majors categories of application software are</string>
    <string name="u3styleText7">1.What are the four categories of application software?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText8">Application software consists of program designed to make users more productive and / or assist them with personal tasks personal tasks. The major categories of application software are <b>business software; graphics and multimedia software; home, personal and educational software;</b> and <b>communications software.</b></string>
    <string name="u3styleText9">Four Categories of Application Software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText10">Business</string>
    <string name="u3styleText11">Graphics and Multimedia</string>
    <string name="u3styleText12">- Word Processing</string>
    <string name="u3styleText13">- Database</string>
    <string name="u3styleText14">- Note Taking</string>
    <string name="u3styleText15">- Personal Information Manager (PIM)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText16">- Business Software for Phones</string>
    <string name="u3styleText17">- Business Software Suite</string>
    <string name="u3styleText18">- Project Management</string>
    <string name="u3styleText19">- Accounting</string>
    <string name="u3styleText20">- Document Management</string>
    <string name="u3styleText21">- Enterprise computing</string>
    <string name="u3styleText22">- Computer-Aided Design (CAD)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText23">- Desktop Publishing (for the Professional)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText24">- Paint / Image Editing (for the professional)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText25">- Photo Editing (for the Professional)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText26">- Video and Audio editing (for the Professional)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText27">- Multimedia Authoring</string>
    <string name="u3styleText28">- Web Page Authoring</string>
    <string name="u3styleText29">Home Personal and Educational</string>
    <string name="u3styleText30">Communications</string>
    <string name="u3styleText31">- Software Suite (for Personal Use)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText32">- Personal Finance</string>
    <string name="u3styleText33">- Legal</string>
    <string name="u3styleText34">- TaxPreparation</string>
    <string name="u3styleText35">- Desktop Publishing (for Personal Use)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText36">- Photo Editing and Photo Management (for Personal Use)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText37">- Clip Art / Image Gallery</string>
    <string name="u3styleText38">- Video and Audio Editing (for personal use)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText39">- Home Design/ landscaping</string>
    <string name="u3styleText40">- Travel and Mapping</string>
    <string name="u3styleText41">- Reference and Education</string>
    <string name="u3styleText42">- Entertainment</string>
    <string name="u3styleText43">- Web Browser</string>
    <string name="u3styleText44">- RSS Aggregator</string>
    <string name="u3styleText45">- E-mail</string>
    <string name="u3styleText46">- Blogging</string>
    <string name="u3styleText47">- Instant Messaging</string>
    <string name="u3styleText48">- Newsgroup/Message Board</string>
    <string name="u3styleText49">- Chat Room</string>
    <string name="u3styleText50">- FTP</string>
    <string name="u3styleText51">- Text, Picture, Video Messaging</string>
    <string name="u3styleText52">- ValP</string>
    <string name="u3styleText53">- Video Conferencing</string>
    <string name="u3styleText54">2. What are the seven forms through which software is available?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText55">Application software is available in a variety of forms.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText56">- <b>Packaged software</b> is mass-produced, copy-righted retail software that meets the needs of a variety of users.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText57">- <b>Custom software</b> performs functions specific to a business or industry.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText58">- <b>A web application</b> is a Web site that allows users to access and interact with software from any computer or device that is connected to the Internet.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText59">- <b>Open source software</b> is provided for use, modification, and redistribution.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText60">- <b>Shareware</b> is copy-righted software than is distributed free for a trial period.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText61">- <b>Freeware</b> is copyrighted software provided at no cost by an individual or a company that retains all rights to the software.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText62">- <b>Public-domain software</b> is free software donated for public use and has no copyright restrictions.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText63">3. What are the characteristics of a user interface?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText64">Personal computer operating system often use the concept of a desktop, which is and on-screen work area that has a graphical user interface. One way to start a program in Windows is to move the printer to the Start button on the taskbar and Click the Start button by pressing and releasing a button on the mouse. Then, click the program name on the menu or in a list. Once loaded into memory, the program is displayed in a window on the desktop.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText65">4. What are the key features of widely used business programs?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText66">Business software assists people in becoming more effective and efficient awhile performing daily business activities. Business software includes the following programs.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText67">- <b>Word processing software,</b> sometimes calleda word processor, allows users to create a document by entering text and inserting images, edit the document by making changes, and format the document by changing its appearance.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText68">- <b>Spreadsheet software</b> allows users to organize data in rows and columns, perform calculations, recalculate when data changes, and chart the data.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText69">- <b>Database software</b> allows users to create, access, and manage a database, which is a collection of data organized to allow access, retrieval, and use of that data.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText70">- <b>Presentation software</b> allows users to create a slide show that is displayed on a monitor or projection screen.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText71">- <b>Note taking software</b> enables users to enter typed text, handwritten comments, drawing, or sketches on a page and then save the page as part of a notebook.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText72">- <b>A personal information manager (PIM)</b> includes features to help users organize personal information. In addition to PIM software, a huge variety of business and other software for phones is available.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText73">- <b>A software suit</b> is a collection of individual programs available together as a unit. At a minimum, business software suites include word processing, spreadsheet, e-mail, and presentation programs.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText74">- <b>Project management software</b> allows users to plan, schedule, track, and analyze the events, resources, and costs of a project.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText75">- <b>Accounting software</b> helps companies record and report their financial transactions.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText76">- <b>Document management software</b> provides a means for sharing, distributing, and searching through documents by converting them into a format that can be viewed by any user.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText77">5. What are the key features of widely used graphics and multimedia programs?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText78">Graphics and multimedia software includes the following programs.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText78a">- <b>Computer-aided design (CAD)</b> software assists in creating engineering, architectural, and scientific designs.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText79">- <b>Desktop publishing (DTP),</b> software enables professional designers to create sophisticated documents that contain text, graphics and colors.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText80">- <b>Paints software,</b> also called illustration software, lets users draw graphical images with various on-screen tools.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText81">- <b>Image editing software</b> provides the capabilities of paint software and includes the capability to enhance and modify existing images.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText82">- <b>Professional photo editing</b> software is a type of image editing software that allows high-volume digital photo users to edit and customize digital photos.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText83">- <b>Video editing software</b> allows professionals to modify segments of a video.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText84">- <b>Audio editing software</b> lets users modify audio clips, produce studio-quality soundtracks, and add video to video clips.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText85">- <b>Multimedia authoring software</b> allows users to combine text, graphics, audio, video, and animation in interactive application.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText86">- <b>Web page authoring software</b> helps users of all skill levels create. We pages that include graphical images, video, audio, animation, and order special effects with interactive content.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText87">6. What Are the Key Features of Widely Used Home, Personal, and Educational Program?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText88">Software for home, personal, and educational use includes the following program.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText89">- <b>Personal finance software</b> is an accounting program that helps users balance their checkbooks, and evaluate financial plans.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText90">- <b>Legal software</b> assists in the preparation of legal documents.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText91">- <b>Tax preparation</b> software guides users through filing federal taxes.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText92">- <b>Personal DTP software</b> helps users create newsletters, brochures, flyers, advertisements, greeting and business cards, logos, and Web pages.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText93">- <b>Personal paint/image editing</b> software provides an easy-to-use interface with functions tailored to meet the needs of home and small business users.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText94">- <b>Personal photo editing software</b> is a type of image editing software used to edit digital photos. Photo management software helps users view, organize, sort, catalog, and share digital photos.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText95">- Application software often includes a <b>clip art/image gallery,</b> which is a collection of clip art and photos. Video and audio editing software is used to edit home movies, add music or other sounds, and share movies on the Web.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText96">- <b>Home design/landscaping software</b> assists with the design, remodeling, or improvement of a home or landscape.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText97">- <b>Travel and mapping software</b> enables users to view maps, determine route directions, and locate points of interest.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText98">- <b>Reference software</b> provides valuable and thorough information for all individuals.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText99">- <b>Educational software</b> teaches a particular skill.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText100">- <b>Entertainment software</b> includes interactive games, videos, and other programs to support hobbies or provide amusement.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText101">7. What Are the Advantages of and Ways to Access Web Applications?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText102">A Web application, or <i>Web app,</i> require less disk space on a computer than installed software and is less costly to upgrade. Users often interact with Web applications directly at the Web site, referred to as the host, through their Web browser. Some Web sites require that you download the software to your computer or device.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText103">8. What Are the Types of Application Software Used in Communications?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText1104">Application software for communications includes Web browsers to access and view Web pages; e-mail programs to transmit message via a network; instant messaging software for real-time exchange of messages or files; chat room software to have real-time, online typed conversations; text, picture, and video messaging software; RSS aggregator program to keep track of changes made to Web sites; <i>blog software,</i> or <i>blogware,</i> to create and maintain a blog; newsgroup/message board programs that allow online written discussion; FTP program to upload and download files on the Internet; VoIT(Internet telephony), which allows users to speak to other users over the Internet; and video conferencing software for meeting on a network.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText105">9. What Learning Aids Are Available for Application Software?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText106">To assist in the learning process, many programs offer Help features.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText107">- <b>Online Help</b> is the electronic equivalent of a user manual. Most online Help links to Web-based Help, which provides updates and more comprehensive resources. Popular in business, industry, and schools.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText108">- <b>Web-based training(WBT)</b> is a type of computer-based</string>
    <string name="u3styleText109">Practice</string>
    <string name="u3styleText110">1. What are the four categories of application?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText111">2. Fill in the table of the four categories of application software.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText112">Business Software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText113">Graphics and Multimedia software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText114">Home/ Personal / Education software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText115">Communication software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText116">3. Click T for True and F for False.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText117">1. The categories of application software are mutually exclusive.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText118">2. A dialog box is a window that provides information, presents available option, or requests a response.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText119">3. A font is a name assigned to a specific design of characters.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText120">4. A front is name assigned to a specific design of characters.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText121">5. To click a button on the screen requires moving the pointer to the button and then pressing and holding down a button on the mouse. (usually the right mouse button)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText122">True</string>
    <string name="u3styleText123">False</string>
    <string name="u3styleText124">4. Multiple ChoiceSelect the best answer.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText125">1. ………………….. Is mass-produced, copyrighted retail software that meets the needs of a wide variety of users, not just a single user of company.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText126">a. Open source software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText127">b. A Web application</string>
    <string name="u3styleText128">c. Custom software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText129">d. Packaged software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText130">2. ………………….. Is a collection individual programs available together as a unit.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText131">a. Shareware</string>
    <string name="u3styleText132">b. A software suite</string>
    <string name="u3styleText133">c. Packaged software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText134">d. Custom software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText135">3. ……………………allows a user to plan, schedule, track, and analyze the events, resources, and costs of a project.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText136">a. Document management software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText137">b. Accounting software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText138">c. Project management software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText139">d. CAD software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText140">4. ………………… software provides a means for sharing, distributing, and searching through documents by converting them into a format theatcan be viewed by any user.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText141">a. Word processing</string>
    <string name="u3styleText142">b. Document management</string>
    <string name="u3styleText143">c. Portable Document Format (PDF)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText144">d. Database</string>
    <string name="u3styleText145">5. …………………… is the electronic equivalent of a user manual.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText146">a. Online Help</string>
    <string name="u3styleText147">b. Web-based training</string>
    <string name="u3styleText148">c. E-learning</string>
    <string name="u3styleText149">d. Distance learning</string>
    <string name="u3styleText150">6. A(n)………………… is an online area where users have written discussions</string>
    <string name="u3styleText151">a. FTP Program</string>
    <string name="u3styleText152">b .Web browser</string>
    <string name="u3styleText153">c. text message</string>
    <string name="u3styleText154">d. Newsgroup/ message board</string>
    <string name="u3styleText155">7. With ……………., you can view, organize, sort, catalog, print and share digital photos.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText156">a. desktop publishing software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText157">b. clip art</string>
    <string name="u3styleText158">c. Photo management software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText159">d. Spreadsheet software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText160">8. ……………….helps home and small business users create newsletters, brochures, advertisements, postcards, greeting cards, letterhead, business cards, banners, calendars, logos, and Web pages.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText161">a. Note taking software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText162">b. Personal DTP software</string>
    <string name="u3styleText163">c. Blog ware</string>
    <string name="u3styleText164">d. A personal information manager</string>
    <string name="u3styleText165">You are going to listen how to save a file in application software. The learn how to activities step you through fundamental technology skills when using a computer. The learn how to exercises enable you to become more proficient with these skills.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText166">Listening</string>
    <string name="u3styleText167">Now listen how to save a file in application software and order each step into the right steps.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText168">When you use application software, usually you either will create a new file or modify and existing file. If you turn off your computer or lose electrical power while working on the file, the file will not be retained. In order to retain the file, you must save it.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText169">To save a new file, you must complete several tasks:</string>
    <string name="u3styleText170">Click the save button to save the file.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText171">Designate where the file should be stored. This includes indemnifying both the device (such as drive C) and the folder or library</string>
    <string name="u3styleText172">Initiate and action indicating you want to save the file, such as selecting. Save on the File menu.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText173">Specify the name of the file.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText174">Language work</string>
    <string name="u3styleText175">Structure</string>
    <string name="u3styleText176">Present Continuous Tense</string>
    <string name="u3styleText177">Affirmative sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText178">Subject + is, am,are + V.ing</string>
    <string name="u3styleText179">Interrogative Sentence (WHQuestion)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText180">What,When, Where, Why, Who, How + is, am, are + Subject + V.ing+?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText181">Interrogative Sentence (Yes/ No Question)</string>
    <string name="u3styleText182">Is, Am,Are + Subject + V.ing?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText183">Negative Sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText184">Subject + is, am, are +not + V.ing</string>
    <string name="u3styleText185">Example</string>
    <string name="u3styleText186">Affirmative sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText187">Example:I am playing computer games</string>
    <string name="u3styleText188">Interrogative sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText189">1) Wh-question sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText190">Example: What are you doing now?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText191">2) Yes/ No question</string>
    <string name="u3styleText192">Example: Are you playing computer games?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText193">Negative sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText194">Example: I’m not playing computer games.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText195">Practice</string>
    <string name="u3styleText196">Look at the picture and make four sentences</string>
    <string name="u3styleText197">Example</string>
    <string name="u3styleText198">1. Wh-question sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText199">\t\t\tWhat is Nan doing?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText200">2. Interrogative sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText201">\t\t\tNan is playing computer games.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText202">3. Yes/ No question sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText203">\t\t\tIs Nan playing computer games?</string>
    <string name="u3styleText204">4. Negative sentence</string>
    <string name="u3styleText205">\t\t\tNan isn’t playing computer games.</string>
    <string name="u3styleText197e">5. They .......</string>
    <string name="u3styleText197d">4. Windy .......</string>
    <string name="u3styleText197c">3. Emily .......</string>
    <string name="u3styleText197b">2. Colin .......</string>
    <string name="u3styleText197a">1. Tony .......</string>
    <string name="u3styleText197f">Nan ........</string>


    <!--post unit1-->
    <string name="postUnit1styleText1">Post-test</string>
    <string name="postUnit1styleText5">6. What is a computer?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1styleText10">8. What does CPU stand for?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1styleText15">2. An ……………… device is any hardware component that allows you to enter data and instructions into a computer.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1styleText20">9. Three commonly used ………………… device are a printer, a monitor, and speakers.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1styleText25">5. ……………… is any electronic or mechanical part you can see or touch.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1styleText30">3. Which are the components of a computer?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1styleText35">7. Which are input devices?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1styleText40">10. Which is not an output device?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1styleText45">1. Which is not a storage device?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1styleText50">4. Describe this diagram by using given words.</string>

    <!--pre unit1-->
    <string name="preUnit1styleText1">Pre-test</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText2">Unit 1</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText3">Computer Users</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText4">Direction: Choose the best answer.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText5">1. What is a computer?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText6">a. It’s an appliance device which can accept data in a certain form, process the data and give the results of the processing.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText7">b. It’s an electronic device which can accept data in a certain form, process the data and give the results of the processing.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText8">c. It’s a motorized device that processes output into input.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText9">d. It’s a storage device records writes and retrieves reads items to and from storage media.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText10">2. What does CPU stand for?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText11">a. Central Processing Unity</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText12">b. Central Processing United</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText13">c. Central Processing Unit</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText14">d. Central Programming Unit</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText15">3. An ……………… device is any hardware component that allows you to enter data and instructions into a computer.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText16">a. input</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText17">b. output</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText18">c. electronic</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText19">d. external</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText20">4. Three commonly used ………………… device are a printer, a monitor, and speakers.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText21">a. input</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText22">b. output</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText23">c. electronic</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText24">d. external</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText25">5. ……………… is any electronic or mechanical part you can see or touch.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText26">a. Software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText27">b. Hardware</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText28">c. Storage device</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText29">d. Speaker</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText30">6. Which are the components of a computer?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText31">a. Input devices, Output devices, System unit, Storage devices and Communication devices.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText32">b. Input devices, Output devices, System unit, Storage devices and External devices.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText33">c. Input devices, Output devices, System unit, Storage devices and Control devices.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText34">d. Input devices, Output devices, Stem unit, Storage devices and Communication devices.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText35">7. Which are input devices?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText36">a. speakers, printers and monitor</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText37">b. card reader, USB flash drive and memory cards</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText38">c. microphone, modem and external hard disk</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText39">d. scanners, keyboards and mouse</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText40">8. Which is not an output device?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText41">a. A printer</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText42">b. A speaker</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText43">c. A monitor</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText44">d. A keyboard</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText45">9. Which is not a storage device?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText46">a. A memory card</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText47">b. A hard disk drive</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText48">c. A scanner</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText49">d. An external hard disk</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText50">10. Describe this diagram by using given words.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText51">Peripherals</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText52">Input devices</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText53">Output devices</string>
    <string name="preUnit1styleText54">Storage media</string>


    <!--post unit2-->
    <string name="postUnit2styleText1">Post-test</string>
    <string name="postUnit2styleText5">6. What are the main parts of the CPU?</string>
    <string name="postUnit2styleText10">2. What does ALU stand for?</string>
    <string name="postUnit2styleText15">9. What does ALU do?</string>
    <string name="postUnit2styleText20">4. What type of memory is temporary?</string>
    <string name="postUnit2styleText25">7. What type of memory is permanent and includes instructions needed by the CPU?</string>
    <string name="postUnit2styleText30">5. If you want to change the capital letters permanently, what should you do?</string>
    <string name="postUnit2styleText35">1. If you want to change to capital letter, what should you do?</string>
    <string name="postUnit2styleText40">8. ........ appears to the right of the main keyboard. The NumLock key is used to switch from numbers to editing keys.</string>
    <string name="postUnit2styleText45">3. What do you call the mouse which doesn\'t have a ball?</string>
    <string name="postUnit2styleText50">10. Scanners, printers and webcams are ……………………</string>

    <!--pre unit2-->
    <string name="preUnit2styleText1">Pre-test</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText2">Unit 2</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText3">Computer Architecture</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText4">Direction: Choose the best answer.</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText5">1. What are the main parts of the CPU?</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText6">a. Hardware and software</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText7">b. Keyboard output devices</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText8">c. Storage devices</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText9">d. Hard disks</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText10">2. What does ALU stand for?</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText11">a. Architecture Logic Unit</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText12">b. Arithmetic Logic Unit</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText13">c. Artificial Logic Unit</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText14">d. Arithmetic Login Unit</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText15">3. What does ALU do?</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText16">a. To store information</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText17">b. To control data</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText18">c. To perform mathematical calculations</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText19">d. To feed information</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText20">5. What type of memory is temporary?</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText21">a. RAM</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText22">b. ROM</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText23">c. Cards</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText24">d. BIOS</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText25">6. What type of memory is permanent and includes instructions needed by the CPU?</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText26">a. Ram</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText27">b. ROM</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText28">c. Cards</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText29">d. BIOS</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText30">7. If you want to change the capital letters permanently, what should you do?</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText31">a. Press the caps lock key</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText32">b. Press the tab key</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText33">c. Press the alt key</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText34">d. Press the shift key</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText35">8. If you want to change to capital letter, what should you do?</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText36">a. Press the caps lock key</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText37">b. Press the tab key</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText38">c. Press the alt key</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText39">d. Press the shift key</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText40">9. ........ appears to the right of the main keyboard. The NumLock key is used to switch from numbers to editing keys.</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText41">a. Cursor control key</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText42">b. Alphanumeric key</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText43">c. Function key</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText44">d. A numeric keypad</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText45">10. What do you call the mouse which doesn\'t have a ball?</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText46">a. An optical mouse</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText47">b. An option mouse</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText48">c. An alternative mouse</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText49">d. An alphabet mouse</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText50">4. Scanners, printers and webcams are ……………………</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText51">a. extras</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText52">b. peripherals</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText53">c. externals</string>
    <string name="preUnit2styleText54">d. internals</string>


    <!--post unit3-->
    <string name="postUnit3styleText1">Post-test</string>
    <string name="postUnit3styleText5">2. ……………. is mass-produced, copyrighted retail software that meets the need of a wide variety of users, not just a single user or company.</string>
    <string name="postUnit3styleText10">4. ………………….. is a collection of individual programs available together as a unit.</string>
    <string name="postUnit3styleText15">7. ………………… software provides a means for sharing, distributing, and searching through documents by converting them into a format that can be viewed by any user.</string>
    <string name="postUnit3styleText20">9. ……………………allows a user to plan, schedule, track, and analyze the events, resources, and costs of a project.</string>
    <string name="postUnit3styleText25">1. A(n)………………… is an online area where users have written discussions.</string>
    <string name="postUnit3styleText30">10. …………………… is the electronic equivalent of a user manual.</string>
    <string name="postUnit3styleText35">8. With ……………., you can view, organize, sort, catalog, print and share digital photos.</string>
    <string name="postUnit3styleText40">6. ……………….helps home and small business users create newsletters, brochures, advertisements, postcards, greeting cards, letterhead, business cards, banners, calendars, logos, and Web pages.</string>
    <string name="postUnit3styleText45">5. ………………… software is available to the public at no cost.</string>
    <string name="postUnit3styleText50">3. Some …………………….is considered system software because it works with hardware and transmission media.</string>

    <!--pre unit3-->
    <string name="preUnit3styleText1">Pre-test</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText2">Unit 3</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText3">Computer Applications</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText4">Direction: Choose the best answer.</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText5">1. ……………. is mass-produced, copyrighted retail software that meets the need of a wide variety of users, not just a single user or company.</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText6">a. Packaged software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText7">b. A Web application</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText8">c. Open source software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText9">d. Custom software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText10">2. ………………….. is a collection of individual programs available together as a unit.</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText11">a. Shareware</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText12">b. A software suite</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText13">c. Packaged software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText14">d. Custom software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText15">3. ………………… software provides a means for sharing, distributing, and searching through documents by converting them into a format that can be viewed by any user.</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText16">a. Word processing</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText17">b. Document management</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText18">c. Portable Document Format (PDF)</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText19">d. Database</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText20">4. ……………………allows a user to plan, schedule, track, and analyze the events, resources, and costs of a project.</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText21">a. Document management software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText22">b. Accounting software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText23">c. Project management software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText24">d. CAD software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText25">5. A(n)………………… is an online area where users have written discussions.</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText26">a. FTP Program</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText27">b. Web browser</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText28">c. text message</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText29">d. Newsgroup/ message board</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText30">6. …………………… is the electronic equivalent of a user manual.</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText31">a. Online Help</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText32">b. Web-based training</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText33">c. E-learning</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText34">d. Distance learning</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText35">7. With ……………., you can view, organize, sort, catalog, print and share digital photos.</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText36">a. desktop publishing software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText37">b. clip art</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText38">c. Photo management software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText39">d. Spreadsheet software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText40">8. ……………….helps home and small business users create newsletters, brochures, advertisements, postcards, greeting cards, letterhead, business cards, banners, calendars, logos, and Web pages.</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText41">a. Note taking software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText42">b. Personal DTP software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText43">c. Blog ware</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText44">d. A personal information manager</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText45">9. ………………… software is available to the public at no cost.</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText46">a. Packaged</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText47">b. Custom</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText48">c. Open source</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText49">d. Public-domain</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText50">10. Some …………………….is considered system software because it works with hardware and transmission media.</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText51">a. communication software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText52">b. business software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText53">c. application software</string>
    <string name="preUnit3styleText54">d. project management software</string>


    <!--unit4-->
    <string name="u4styleText1">Unit 4</string>
    <string name="u4styleText2">The internet</string>
    <string name="u4styleText3">Objective</string>
    <string name="u4styleText4">At the end of this unit, students are able to describe the types of Internet access providers: Internet service providers, online service providers, wireless Internet service providers</string>
    <string name="u4styleText7">a. A wireless fidelity network uses radio signals to provide high-speed.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText5">Warm-up</string>
    <string name="u4styleText6">1.What is the Internet?</string>
    <string name="u4styleText8">b. A wide-area network spanning the globe.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText9">2. What do you often do on the Internet?</string>
    <string name="u4styleText10">What do you often do on the Internet? Oder the important by choosing 1&#45;5(no score)</string>
    <string name="u4styleText11">\t\t\t5 = always do on the Internet</string>
    <string name="u4styleText12">\t\t\t4 = usually do on the Internet</string>
    <string name="u4styleText13">\t\t\t3 = often do on the Internet</string>
    <string name="u4styleText14">\t\t\t2 = sometimes do on the Internet</string>
    <string name="u4styleText15">\t\t\t1 = occasionally do on the Internet</string>
    <string name="u4styleText16">• Look up information</string>
    <string name="u4styleText17">• Schoolwork, jobs, how-to, research, banking, directions, businesses, Email</string>
    <string name="u4styleText18">• Buy and sell products</string>
    <string name="u4styleText19">• Social networking (Facebook, twitter, blogs)</string>
    <string name="u4styleText20">• Share with friends and others what you’re doing, including sharing pictures and videos</string>
    <string name="u4styleText21">• Watch and post videos</string>
    <string name="u4styleText22">• News and weather</string>
    <string name="u4styleText23">• Watch and post videos</string>
    <string name="u4styleText24">• News and weather</string>
    <string name="u4styleText25">• Gas prices</string>
    <string name="u4styleText26">• Games</string>
    <string name="u4styleText27">• Take college courses (MOOC)</string>
    <string name="u4styleText28">• Monitor your home when you are away</string>
    <string name="u4styleText29">• Financial transactions; e.g. banking, stock market, pay bills</string>
    <string name="u4styleText30">• View patents on the Patent/Trademark web site</string>
    <string name="u4styleText31">Presentation</string>
    <string name="u4styleText32">1. The internet’s History</string>
    <string name="u4styleText33">The internet, also called the Net, is a worldwide collection of networks that links millions of businesses, government agencies, educational institutions, and individuals. The Internet has its roots in ARPANET, a network started in 1969 to link scientific and academic researchers across the United States. In 1986, the National Science Foundation connected its huge network, called NSF net, to ARPANET, creating a configuration of complex networks and hosts that became known as the Internet. Today, more than 550 million bostcomputers connect to the Internet.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText34">2. What are the various types of the Internet connections?</string>
    <string name="u4styleText35">Many home and small business users connect to the Internet via high-speed broadband Internet service. With broadband Internet service, your computer or mobile device usually is connected to the Internet the entire time it is powered on. Examples of broadband Internet service include cable, DSL, fiber, radio signals and satellite.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText37">- <b>Cable Internet service</b> provides high-speed Internet access through the cable television network via a cable modern.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText39">- <b>DSL. (digital subscriber line)</b> provides high-speed Internet connection using regular copper telephone lines.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText41">- <b>Fiber to the Premises (FTTP)</b> uses fiber-optic cable to provide high-speed Internet access to home and business users.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText43">- <b>Fixed wireless</b> offers high-speed Internet connections using a dish-shaped antenna on your house or business to communicate with a tower location via radio signals.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText45">- <b>A cellular radio network</b> high-speed Internet connections to devices with built-in compatible technology or computers with wireless moderns.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText47">- <b>A Wi-Fi (wireless fidelity)</b> network uses radio signals to provide high-speed Internet connections to compatible or properly equipped wireless computers and devices.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText48">3. What are the types of Internet Access providers?</string>
    <string name="u4styleText49">An access provider is a business that provides access to the Internet free of for a fee.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText51">- <b>An ISP (Internet service provider)</b> is a regional or national access provider.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText53">- <b>An online service provider (OSP)</b> provides Internet access in addition to members-only features.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText55">- <b>A wireless Internet service provider</b> provides wireless Internet access to desktop and notebook computers and mobile devices with built-in wireless capabilities (such as Wi&#45;Fi) or to computers using wireless moderns or wireless access devices.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText56">4. Internet Addresses</string>
    <string name="u4styleText57">What is the purpose of an IP Address, and what is its relationship to a domain name?</string>
    <string name="u4styleText59">- <b>An IP address (Internet Protocol address)</b> is a number that uniquely identifies each computer of device connected to the Internet. The internet relies on IP addresses to send data to computers at specific locations. The IP address usually consists of four groups of numbers, each separated by a period.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText61">- <b>A domain name</b> is the text version of an IP address.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText62"><![CDATA[IP address ==> 72.14.207.99]]></string>
    <string name="u4styleText63"><![CDATA[Domain name ==> www.google.com]]></string>
    <string name="u4styleText64">For example, www.Philips.com.au is the domain name for Philips Australia.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText65">Examples of Generic Top-Level Domains</string>
    <string name="u4styleText66">TLD</string>
    <string name="u4styleText67">Intended Purpose</string>
    <string name="u4styleText68">aero</string>
    <string name="u4styleText69">Aviation community members</string>
    <string name="u4styleText70">biz</string>
    <string name="u4styleText71">Businesses of all sizes</string>
    <string name="u4styleText72">cat</string>
    <string name="u4styleText73">Catalan cultural community</string>
    <string name="u4styleText74">com</string>
    <string name="u4styleText75">Commercial organizations, businesses, and companies</string>
    <string name="u4styleText76">coop</string>
    <string name="u4styleText77">Business cooperatives such as credit unions and rural electric co-ops</string>
    <string name="u4styleText78">edu</string>
    <string name="u4styleText79">Educational institutions</string>
    <string name="u4styleText80">gov</string>
    <string name="u4styleText81">Government agencies</string>
    <string name="u4styleText82">info</string>
    <string name="u4styleText83">Business organizations orindividuals providing general information</string>
    <string name="u4styleText84">5. The world wide web</string>
    <string name="u4styleText85">What is the purpose of a web browser, and What are the components of a web address?</string>
    <string name="u4styleText87">- <b>A web browser,</b> or <b>browser,</b> is application software that allows users to access and view Web pages or access Web2.0 programs. With an Internet connection established, you start a Web browser, which then retrieves and displays a starting Web page, sometimes called <b>a home page.</b> The home page usually contains links to other Web pages.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText89">- <b>A link,</b> short for hyperlink, is a built-in connection to another related Web page or part of a Web page. A another related Web page or part of a Web page. <b>A web page</b> has a unique address called a URL. (Uniform Resource locator), or <b>Web address. A Web address</b> consists of a protocol, a domain name, and sometimes the path to a specific Web page or location on a Web page.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText89a">The example of the web address in the address bar.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText89b">6. What\'s the difference between the Web and the internet?</string>
    <string name="u4styleText89c">Some people think that the internet and the Web are the same thing, but in fact they are different. The internet (often called simply \"the net\") is a global network of interconnected computers. These computers communicate with each other over existing telecommunications networks – principally, the telephone system. The Word Wide Web (usually known as just \"the Web\") is the billions of web pages that are stored on large computers called web servers. To access the web, you need a computer and a modem. You then connect over your telephone line to an internet service provider (ISP), which sends your request to view a particular web page to the correct web server. Websites are not the only service available on the internet. It is also used for many other functions, including sending and receiving email, and connecting to newsgroups and 6 discussion groups. You could say that the internet is a system of roads, and web pages and emails are types of traffic that travel on those roads.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText90">7. How do you use a search engine to search for information on the web, and what is the difference between a search engine and a subject directory?</string>
    <string name="u4styleText92">- <b>A search engine</b> is a program that finds Web sites, web pages, images, videos, news, maps and other information related to a specific topic. To use a search engine, you enter a word or phrase, called search text or a search query, that describes the item you want to find. Each word in the search text is known as a keyword. The search engine displays a list of bits. When clicked, each hit displays an associated Web site our Web page. A subject directory classifies Web pages in an organized set of categories and related subcategories. By clicking links, you move through levels to display a list of Web pages about a desired topic.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText93">How to use a Search Engine</string>
    <string name="u4styleText94">8. What are the types of web sites?</string>
    <string name="u4styleText96">- <b>A portal</b> is a Web site that offers a variety of Internet services from a single location. A news Web site contains newsworthy material. An information Web site contains factual information. A business. Marketing Web site promotes or sells products or services.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText98">- <b>A blog,</b> short for Weblog, is an informal Web site consisting of time-stamped articles, or posts, in a diary or journal format, usually listed in reverse chronological order.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText100">- <b>A wiki</b> is a collaborative Web site that allows users to create, add to, modify, or delete the Web site content via their Web browser.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText102">- <b>An online social network,</b> or <b>social networking Web site,</b> encourages members to share this interests, ideas, stories, photos, music, and videos with other registered users. An education Web site offers avenues for teaching and learning . An entertainment Web site provides and interactive and engaging environment. An advocacy Web site describes a cause, opinion, or idea.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText104">- <b>A web application,</b> or <b>Web app,</b> is a Web site that allows users to access and interact with software through a Web browser or any computer or device connected to the Internet.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText106">- <b>A content aggregator</b> is a business that</string>
    <string name="u4styleText107">9. How do web pages use graphics, animation, audio, video, virtual reality, and plug-ins?</string>
    <string name="u4styleText108">Some Web pages use <b>multimedia,</b> which combines text with graphics, animation, audio, video, and /or virtual reality</string>
    <string name="u4styleText110">- <b>A graphic</b> is a digital representation of non text information such as a drawing, chart, or photo.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText112">- <b>Animation</b> is the appearance of motion created by displaying a series of still images in sequence.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText114">- <b>Audio</b> includes music, speech, or any other sound.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText116">- <b>Video</b> consists of full-motion images played back at various speeds.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText118">- <b>Virtual reality (VR)</b> is the use of computers to simulate and environment that appears as three-dimensional space.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText120">- <b>A plug-in,</b> or <b>add-on ,</b> is a program that extends a browser’s capability to display multimedia elements.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText121">10. What are the types of E-commerce?</string>
    <string name="u4styleText123">- <b>E-commerce,</b> short for electronic commerce, is a business transaction that occurs over an electronic network such as the Internet&#45;Business&#45;to &#45;commerce (B2C) e&#45;commerce consists of the sale of goods and services to the general public. Consumer&#45;to&#45;consumer (C2C) e&#45;commerce occurs when one consumer sells directly to another, such a in an online auction. Business&#45;to&#45;business (B2B) e&#45;commerce takes place between businesses that exchange goods and services.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText124">Practice 1</string>
    <string name="u4styleText125">Write the meaning of these abbreviations.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText126">DSL</string>
    <string name="u4styleText127">FTTP</string>
    <string name="u4styleText129">ISP</string>
    <string name="u4styleText130">OSP</string>
    <string name="u4styleText131">A Wi-Fi</string>
    <string name="u4styleText132">IP</string>
    <string name="u4styleText133">URL</string>
    <string name="u4styleText134">Practice 2</string>
    <string name="u4styleText135">Direction: Click T for True and F for False.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText136">1. The Internet is a wide&#45;area network spanning the globe.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText137">True</string>
    <string name="u4styleText138">False</string>
    <string name="u4styleText139">2. The Web is an infrastructure of distributed information combined with the software that uses networks as a vehicle to exchange that information.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText140">3. A URL is the standard way of specifying the location of a web page.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText141">4. The Internet and the Web are essentially two names for the same thing.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText142">5. The computer that is set up to respond to web requests is a web browser.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText143">6. When we visit a website, we actually bring the site to us.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText144">7. Most search engines use a context-based approach for finding candidate pages.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText145">8. You must have a web browser in order to access the Web.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText146">9. DSL, provides high-speed Internet connections through the cable television network.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText147">10. In general, the first portion of each IP address identifies the network and the last portion identifies the specific computer.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText148">Practice 3: Common domain name extensions include.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText149">Direction: Fill in the blanks.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText150">.com</string>
    <string name="u4styleText151">Education institutions</string>
    <string name="u4styleText152">.gov</string>
    <string name="u4styleText153">.org</string>
    <string name="u4styleText154">Military organizations</string>
    <string name="u4styleText155">.tel</string>
    <string name="u4styleText156">Network providers or commercial companies</string>
    <string name="u4styleText157">Listening</string>
    <string name="u4styleText158">Now listen how to use a search engine and match each with a picture.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText158a">• Click the Google Search button. When the results of the search are displayed, scroll through the links and read the descriptions. Point to the Aspen Snow mass link.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText158b">• Type the search engine’s web address in the address bar in the web browser.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText158c">• Click the Aspen Snowmass link to display a Web page with a description and links to skiing in Aspen.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText158d">• Press the Enter key. When the Google home page is displayed type. Aspen Colorado ski resorts as the search text and then point to the Google Search button.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText159">Language Work</string>
    <string name="u4styleText160">Warnings.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText161">Where might you see these warnings?</string>
    <string name="u4styleText162">1. Never give out your home address or phone number?</string>
    <string name="u4styleText163">2. This appliance must be earthed.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText164">3. Avoid turning off main power while computer is running.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText165">4. No smoking, eating or drinking at the computer.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText166">5. A machine which has been exposed to a moist atmosphere should be given time to dry out before being put into use.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText167">Warnings are used to ensure safety, to prevent damage to equipment and breaches of security, and to ensure the law is not broken. The simplest warnings are basic instructions Not to do something:</string>
    <string name="u4styleText168">*Don’t +V1</string>
    <string name="u4styleText169">Example: Don’t give your password.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText170">*Avoid + Ving</string>
    <string name="u4styleText171">Example: Avoid drinking turning off main power while computer is running.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText172">*No + Ving</string>
    <string name="u4styleText173">Example: No smoking, eating or drinking at the computer.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText174">*Never + Verb</string>
    <string name="u4styleText175">Example: Never give out your home address or phone number.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText176">Warnings may be made stronger by using must / must not and in some cases should / should not.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText177">For example:</string>
    <string name="u4styleText178">The wire linking a static earthing band to earth must contain a resistor of at least 1 meg ohm.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText179">Language work:</string>
    <string name="u4styleText180">Practice 1</string>
    <string name="u4styleText181">Direction: Rewrite each of these warnings according to the prompt.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText182">1. Don’t give open access to PCs.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText183">Avoid</string>
    <string name="u4styleText184">2. You must not use your own programs on these machines.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText185">Never</string>
    <string name="u4styleText186">3. No coffee in this lab.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText187">must not</string>
    <string name="u4styleText188">4. Avoid giving financial information in a chat room.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText189">Don’t</string>
    <string name="u4styleText190">5. Never give out your password.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText191">must not</string>
    <string name="u4styleText192">6. Don’t use out&#45;of&#45;date anti&#45;virus software.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText193">Avoid</string>
    <string name="u4styleText194">Language work:</string>
    <string name="u4styleText195">Practice 2</string>
    <string name="u4styleText196">Direction: Rewrite each of these warnings according to the prompt.</string>
    <string name="u4styleText197">\tmust not, you, your, programs, these, machines, use, own,on</string>
    <string name="u4styleText198">\tin, coffee, this, room, no</string>
    <string name="u4styleText199">\tremove, ICs, don’t, with, screwdriver, a</string>
    <string name="u4styleText200">\tavoid, out-of-date, using, anti-virus, software</string>
    <string name="u4styleText201">\tturning off, avoid, power, while, main, is, computer, running</string>



    <!--post unit4-->
    <string name="postUnit4styleText1">Post-test</string>
    <string name="postUnit4styleText5">3. The internet (often called simply \'the net\') is a global …………………………….of interconnected computers.</string>
    <string name="postUnit4styleText10">1. ADSL* is more commonly known as ……………………………………</string>
    <string name="postUnit4styleText15">10. Before you can connect to the internet for the first time, you have to …………………………………… an account with an ISP.</string>
    <string name="postUnit4styleText20">9. Looking at web pages can be called \"navigating the Web\" but is more commonly called ………………………….</string>
    <string name="postUnit4styleText25">2. Which can keep a public diary of your journey through South America?</string>
    <string name="postUnit4styleText30">8. If you want to find out about the First World War, where should you find it?</string>
    <string name="postUnit4styleText35">4. If you want to exchange messages in real time with friends or colleagues, which the Internet features should you use?</string>
    <string name="postUnit4styleText42">5. Exchange messages in real time about anything you like with strangers.</string>
    <string name="postUnit4styleText43">6. Exchange information and messages about saving a local wood from development with anybody who wants to join in.</string>
    <string name="postUnit4styleText44">7. Post / download photos, video clips and messages among a group of friends.</string>

    <!--pre unit4-->
    <string name="preUnit4styleText1">Pre-test</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText2">Unit4</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText3">The Internet</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText4">Choose the best answer.</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText5">1. The internet (often called simply \'the net\') is a global …………………………….of interconnected computers.</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText6">a. net</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText7">b. network</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText8">c. warming</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText9">d. Presenting</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText10">2. ADSL* is more commonly known as ……………………………………</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText11">a. longband</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText12">b. broadband</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText13">c. wideband</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText14">d. webband</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText15">3. Before you can connect to the internet for the first time, you have to …………………………………… an account with an ISP.</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText16">a. set</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText17">b. set up</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText18">c. set in</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText19">d. set out</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText20">4. Looking at web pages can be called \"navigating the Web\" but is more commonly called ………………………….</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText21">a. \"surfing the net\"</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText22">b. \"skiing the net\"</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText23">c. \"swimming the net\"</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText24">d. \"searching the net\"</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText25">5. Which can keep a public diary of your journey through South America?</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText26">a. Blog</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText27">b. Webmail</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText28">c. Online radio</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText29">d. Portal</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText30">6. If you want to find out about the First World War, where should you find it?</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText31">a. instant massaging</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText32">b. online encyclopedia</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText33">c. portal</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText34">d. chatroom</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText35">7. If you want to exchange messages in real time with friends or colleagues, which the Internet features should you use?</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText36">a. currency converter</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText37">b. instant messaging</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText38">c. online casino</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText39">d. Blog</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText40">Match these activities with the Internet features. (8-10)</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText41">\ta. Newsgroup \t\t\t\tb. forum\n\tc. discussing group\n\td. Bulletin board/ noticeboard\n\te. chat room</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText42">8. Exchange messages in real time about anything you like with strangers.</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText43">9. Exchange information and messages about saving a local wood from development with anybody who wants to join in.</string>
    <string name="preUnit4styleText44">10. Post / download photos, video clips and messages among a group of friends.</string>


    <!--unit 5-->
    <string name="Unit5styleText1">Unit 5</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText2">Communications systems</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText3">Objectives</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText4">At the end of this unit, students are able to describe these uses of computer communications; wireless messaging services, wireless Internet access points, cybercafé, global positioning system, groupware, voice mail, and Web services</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText5">Warm-up</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText6">What is the purpose of the components required for successful communications?</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText7">a. It is required a sending device, a communication channel and a receiving device.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText8">b. It is required a sending device, a text channel and receiving device.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText9">Presentation</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText10">1. What is the purpose of the components required for successful communications, and what are various sending and receiving devices?</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText11"><b>Computer communication</b> describes a process in which two or more computers or devices transfer data, instructions and information. Successful communications requires <b>a sending device</b> that initiates a transmission instruction, a communications device that connects the sending device to a communications channel to a receiving device, and <b>a receiving device</b> that accepts the transmission of data, instructions, or information. All types of computers and mobile devices serve as sending and receiving devices in a communication system</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText11a">Communications system</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText11b"><b>Picture source:</b> https://techsources.us/communication-software/</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText12">2. How are computer communications used?</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText13">Communications technologies include blogs, chat rooms, e-mail, fax, FTP, instant messaging , newsgroups, RSS, video conferencing, VoIP, Web, Web folders, and wikis. Users can send and receive wireless messages to and from smart phones, cell phones, handheld game consoles, and other mobile devices using <b>text messaging, picture messaging</b> and <b>video messaging,</b> and <b>wireless instant messaging.</b></string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText14">People connect wirelessly to the Internet through <b>a wireless Internet access point.</b> A bot spot is a wireless net-work that provides Internet connection to mobile computers and devices. <b>A cybercafé</b> is a coffeehouse, restaurant, or other location that provides computers with Internet access. <b>A global positioning system (GPS)</b> analyzes signals sent by satellites to determine and earth-based receiver’s geographic location. Many software products provide a means to collaborate, or work online with other users connected to a server. <b>Groupware</b> is a software that helps groups of people work on projects or share information over a net-work . <b>Voice mail</b> allows someone to leave a voice massage for one or more people. Web services describe standardized software that enables programmers to create applications that communicate with other remote computers.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText15">3. What are the advantages of using a Network, and how are LANs, MANs, and WANs different?</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText16"><b>A network</b> is a collection of computers and devices connected together via communications devices and transmission media. Advantages of using a network include facilitating communications, sharing hardware, sharing data and information, sharing software and transferring funds.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText17">Networks typically are classified as a <b>local area network (LAN),</b> which connects computers in devices in a limited geographical area; <b>a metropolitan area network (MAN),</b> which covers a large geographic area using a communications channel that combines many types of media.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText18"><b>A wide area network (WAN)</b> is a network that converts a large geographic area (such as a city, country, or the world) using a communication channel that combines many types of media such as telephone lines, cables, and radio waves. A Wan can be on large network on can consist of two or more LANs connected together. The Internet is the world’s largest WAN.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText19">An example of a WAN</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText20">4. How are a client/ server and peer-to-peer Networks different, and how does a P2P Network work?</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText21">On <b>a client/ server network,</b> one or more computers are as a server, sometimes called a bust computer, which controls access to network resources and provides a centralized storage area, while the other computers and devices on the network are <b>clients</b> that rly on the server for resources. <b>A peer-to-peer network</b> is a simple network that typically connects fewer than 10 computers that have equal responsibilities and capabilities. <b>P2P</b> is and Internet peer-to peer network on which users access each other’s hard disks directly and exchange files over the Internet.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText22">On a client /server network, one or more computes act as a server, and the clients access the server(s).</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText23">Each computer on a peer-to-peer network shares its hardware and software with other computer on the network.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText24">5. How are a star network, Bus network, and Ring network different?</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText25"><b>A network topology</b> refers to the layout of computers and devices in a communications network. There commonly used network topologies are the star bus, and ring. On <b>a star network,</b> all computers and devices on the network connect to a central device, thus forming a star. <b>A bus network</b> consists of a single central cable so which all computers and other devices connect. <b>On a ring network,</b> a cable forms a closed loop (ring) with all computers and devices arranged along the ring.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText26">6. A star network contains a single, centralized hub or switch through.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText27">Devices in a bus network share a single data path.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText27a">On a ring network, all connected devices from a continuous loop.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText28">7. What are various Network Communication Standards?</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText29">A network standard defines guidelines that specify the way computers access a medium, the type(s) of networks, and the type of physical cable or wireless technology used. Network communications standards include the following. <b>Ethernet</b> specifies that no central compute or device on the network should control when data can be transmitted. <b>Token ring</b> requires devices to share or pass a special signal, called a token. <b>TCP/ IP</b>  divides data into packets. <b>Wi-Fi</b> identifies any network based on the 802.11standards for wireless communications. <b>Bluetooth</b> uses short-rang radio waves to transmit data. <b>UWB</b> specifies how to UWB devices use short-rang radio wave to communicate at high speeds. <b>IrDa</b> transmits data wirelessly via infrared light waves. <b>RFID</b> uses radio signals for communications. <b>WiMAX</b> is a network standard developed by IEEE, that specifies how wireless devices communicate over the air in a wide area. The <b>Wireless Application Protocol (WAP)</b> specifies how some mobile devices can devices can display Internet content.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText30">How Electronic RFID Toll Collection Works</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText30a"><b>Step 1</b> Motorist purchases an RFID transponder or RFID tag and attaches it to the vehicle\'s windshield.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText30b"><b>Step 2</b> As the vehicle approaches the tollbooth, the RFID reader in the tollbooth sends a radio wave that activates the windshield-mounted RFID tag. The activated tag sends vehicle information to the RFID reader.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText30c"><b>Step 3</b> The RFID reader sends the vehicle information to the lane controller. The lane controller, which is part of a local area network, transmits the vehicle information to central computer that subtracts the toll from the motorist\'s account. If the vehicle does not have an RFID tag, a high speed camera takes a picture of the license plate and the computer points a violation notice, which is mailed to the motorist. </string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText31">8. What is the purpose of Communication Software?</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText32">Communication software helps users establish a connection to another computer or network; manages the transmission of data, instructions, and information; and provides and interface for users to communicate with one another.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText33">9. What are commonly used communications devices?</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText34">A communications device is hardware capable of transmitting data between a sending device and a receiving device. A dial modem converts digital signals to analog signals and analog signals to digital signals so that data can travel along analog telephone lines. A digital modem sends and receives data and information to and from a digital line. An ISDN modem transits digital data to and from an ISDN line, while a <b>DSL, modem</b> transmits digital data to and from a DSL line. A <b>cable modem,</b> sometimes called a broadband modem, is a digital modem that sends and receives digital data over the cable television network. A <b>wireless modem</b> uses the cell phone network to connect to the Internet wirelessly from mobile computers an devices. A network card enables a computer and device that does not have built-in-networking capability to access a network. A wireless access point allows computers and devices to transfer data wirelessly. A router connects multiple computers or other routers together and transmits data to it correct destination on the network. A bub or switch is a device that provides a central point for cables in a network.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText35">10. How can a Home Network be set up?</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText36">A home network connects multiple computers and devices in a home. An Ethernet network connects each computer to a hub with a physical cable. A home powerline cable network uses the same lines that bring electricity into the house. A phone line network uses existing telephone lines in a home. Most home networks use a Wi-Fi network.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText37">How to set up hardware for a Wi-Fi Home Network?</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText37a"><b>Step 1</b> Sign up for high-speed Internet service, such as through a cable or DSL modem.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText37b"><b>Step 2</b> Using a cable, connect the network, card in a desktop computer to the combination router/wireless access point.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText37c"><b>Step 3</b> Using a cable, connect the combination router/wireless access point to the cable/DSL modem.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText37d"><b>Step 4</b> Install a wireless network card or network adapter in other desktop computers in the home network.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText37e"><b>Step 5</b> Insert a wireless USB network adapter, Express card module, or PC Card in each notebook computer that will access the home network or purchase a notebook computer with built-in wireless networking capability.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText37f"><b>Step 6</b> Purchase a smart phone with built-in wireless capabilities.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText38">Practice</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText39">Direction: Click T for true and F for false.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText40">1. A communication channel is channel is the media on which data, instructions, or information travel.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText41">2. A web video messaging, users can send short video clip, usually about 15 minutes, in addition to all picture messaging services.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText42">3. A network is a collection of computers and devices connected together via communications devices and transmission media.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText43">4. A local area network (LAN) is a network that convers a large geographic area using a communications channel that combines may types of media such as telephone lines, cables, and radio waves.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText44">5. A Web server is a computer that delivers requested Web pages to your computer.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText45">6. An intranet is an internal network that uses Internet technologies.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText46">7. The 40-Gigabit Ethernet standard is the fastest of the Ethernet standards.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText47">8. Bluetooth does not require line-of-sight transmission.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText48">9. At distance 0f 10 meters (about 33 feet), the data transfer rate for UWB devices is 480 Mbps..</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText49">10. Fiber to the Premises (FTTP) uses fiber-optic cable to provide extremely high-speed Internet access to a user’s physical permanent location.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText50">Direction: Select the best answer.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText51">1. With …………………, users can view message detail such as the length of calls and, in some cases, read message contents instead of listening to them.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText52">a. Web services</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText53">b. Internet telephony</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText54">c. Visual voice mail</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText55">d. Video messaging</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText56">2. When an online meeting take place on the web, it is called …………………….</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText57">a. video messaging</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText58">b. a peer-to-peer network</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText59">c. a Web conference</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText60">d. a Web meeting</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText61">3. A document management system ……………………………..</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText62">a. provides for storage and management of a company’s documents.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText63">b. allows users to share documents with other users in real time.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText64">c. prints to a Web address associated with a particular printer.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText65">d. Provides personal information manger functions.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText66">4. A …………………………is a Web application that combines services from two or more sources, creating a new application.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText67">a. document management system</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText68">b. Peer-to peer network</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText69">c. Web service</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText70">d. Mashup</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText71">5. ……………….are devices that provide a common central connection point for nodes on the network.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText72">a. Packets and tokens</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText73">b. Hubs and switches</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText74">c. T1 and T3 lines</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText75">d. Routers and digital modems</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText76">6. ……………………….. Is a standard, specifically a protocol, that defines how a network uses radio signals to communicate with a tag placed in or attached to and object, and animal, or a person.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText77">a. RFID</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText78">b. WiMAX</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText79">c. Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText80">d. UWB</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText81">Listening</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText82">Listen how to install a Wi-Fi Home Network and then order the right steps.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText83">purchase the Wi-Fi equipment</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText84">subscribe to a high-speed Internet access provider</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText85">create the network through the use of software</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText86">connect the physical devices</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText87">Language work</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText87a">Language work</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText87b"><b>Future Tense: Will ==> Form</b></string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText87c"><b><u>Affirmative:</u></b> I <u>will</u> travel to Madrid in October</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText87d"><b><u>Interrogative:</u></b> <u>Will</u> you travel by bus?</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText87e"><b><u>Negative:</u></b> I <u>Will</u> not travel <u>- won\'t</u></string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText87f"><u>Will</u> you travel by train or bus?</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText87g"> I <u>won\'t</u> travel by bus. I <u>will</u> properly travel by train.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText88">Study this list of certainly expressions;</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText89">Practice</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText91">Direction: Order these sentences into future simple tense.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText92">1. will / people/ in / elections / online./ vote</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText93">2. in/ children /my/ country/ have/ will/ all school / mobile phones.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText94">3. will/ robot/ taxis/ controlled./ be</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText95">4. computers / most/ voice-controlled./ will / be</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText96">5. will / be / replaced/ a voice-based/ system./ email/ by</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText97">6. will/ computers/ become/ powerful/ more</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText98">7. transmit/ will /TV journalists/ be/ able to/ what/ by they/ see/ using / in/ their/ sensors/ optic nerves.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText99">8. will /the / way/ we/ communicate/ VoIP phones/ revolutionize</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText100">9. replace/ computers/ mobile phones/ will / as / access/ to/ commonest way/ the/ the Internet.</string>
    <string name="Unit5styleText101">10 . will / have / mobile phones./ pupils / the older/ many</string>

    <!--post unit5-->
    <string name="postUnit5styleText1">Post-test</string>
    <string name="postUnit5styleText5">4. When an online meeting take place on the web, it is called …………………….</string>
    <string name="postUnit5styleText10">2. A document management system ……………………………..</string>
    <string name="postUnit5styleText15">7. With …………………, users can view message detail such as the length of calls and, in some cases, read message contents instead of listening to them.</string>
    <string name="postUnit5styleText20">10. ……………….are devices that provide a common central connection point for nodes on the network.</string>
    <string name="postUnit5styleText25">5. ……………………….. Is a standard, specifically a protocol, that defines how a network uses radio signals to communicate with a tag placed in or attached to and object, and animal, or a person.</string>
    <string name="postUnit5styleText30">1. A …………………………is a Web application that combines services from two or more sources, creating a new application.</string>
    <string name="postUnit5styleText35">9. ……………….Is a wireless network that provides Internet connections to mobile computers or other devices.</string>
    <string name="postUnit5styleText40">6. ……………………….. Is the Internet standard that permits users to upload and download files.</string>
    <string name="postUnit5styleText45">8. What does LAN stand for?</string>
    <string name="postUnit5styleText50">3. What does MAN stand for?</string>

    <!--pre unit5-->
    <string name="preUnit5styleText1">Pre-test</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText2">Unit 5</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText3">Communications system</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText4">Direction: Choose the best answer</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText5">1. When an online meeting take place on the web, it is called …………………….</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText6">a. video messaging</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText7">b. a peer-to-peer network</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText8">c. a Web conference</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText9">d. a Web meeting</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText10">2. A document management system ……………………………..</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText11">a. provides for storage and management of a company’s documents.</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText12">b. allows users to share documents with other users in real time.</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText13">c. prints to a Web address associated with a particular printer.</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText14">d. Provides personal information manger functions.</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText15">3. With …………………, users can view message detail such as the length of calls and, in some cases, read message contents instead of listening to them.</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText16">a. Web services</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText17">b. Internet telephony</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText18">c. Visual voice mail</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText19">d. Video messaging</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText20">4. ……………….are devices that provide a common central connection point for nodes on the network.</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText21">a. Packets and tokens</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText22">b. Hubs and switches</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText23">c. T1 and T3 lines</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText24">d. Routers and digital modems</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText25">5. ……………………….. Is a standard, specifically a protocol, that defines how a network uses radio signals to communicate with a tag placed in or attached to and object, and animal, or a person.</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText26">a. RFID</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText27">b. WiMAX</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText28">c. Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText29">d. UWB</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText30">6. A …………………………is a Web application that combines services from two or more sources, creating a new application.</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText31">a. document management system</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText32">b. Peer-to peer network</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText33">c. Web service</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText34">d. Mashup</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText35">7. ……………….Is a wireless network that provides Internet connections to mobile computers or other devices.</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText36">a. Web conference</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText37">b. Voice mail</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText38">c. A cyber café</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText39">d. Internet</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText40">8. ……………………….. Is the Internet standard that permits users to upload and download files.</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText41">a. Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText42">b. UWB</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText43">c. FTP</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText44">d. A Mashup</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText45">9. What does LAN stand for?</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText46">a. A Local area network</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText47">b. A login area network</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText48">c. A language area network</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText49">d. A land around network</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText50">10. What does MAN stand for?</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText51">a. A microphone area network</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText52">b. A metropolitan area network</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText53">c. A methodology area network</string>
    <string name="preUnit5styleText54">d. A management area network</string>


    <!--post unit1-5-->
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText1">Post-test</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText4">21. Computer literacy, also known as digital literacy, involves having a current knowledge and understanding of……………………………….</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText9">5. ……………………. is/ are a collection of unprocessed items, which can include text, numbers, images, audio, and video.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText14">27. A ……………………….is a specific type of social networking Web site that allows users to cerate a online photo album and store and share their digital photos.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText19">6. A ………………. Is recorded audio stored on a Web site that can be downloaded to a computer or portable media player.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText24">11. …………………….. consists of the programs that control or maintain the operations of the computer and its devices.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText29">29. A (n) ……………….message is a real-time Internet communication, where you exchange messages with other connected users.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText34">30. Many large companies use the word(s), …………………, to refer to the huge network of computers that meets their diverse computing needs.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText39">32. ………………is a system that attempts to imitate the behavior of the human brain.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText44">12. What is a computer?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText49">13. What does CPU stand for?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText54">4. An ……………………….device is any hardware component that allows you to enter data and instructions into a computer.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText59">14. Three commonly used ……………………………device are a printer, a monitor, and speakers.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText64">19. ………………………..is any electronic or mechanical part you can see or touch.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText69">20. Which are the components of a computer?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText74">3. Which are input devices?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText79">22. Which is not an output device?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText84">26. Which is not a storage device?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText89">28. What are the main parts of the CPU?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText94">38. What does ALU stand for?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText99">41. What does ALU do?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText104">47. What type of memory is temporary?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText109">23. What type of memory is permanent and includes instructions needed by the CPU?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText110">44. If you want to change the capital letters permanently, what should you do?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText115">50. Scanners, printers and webcams are ……………………</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText120">8. What do you call the mouse which doesn’t have a ball?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText125">1. ……………….. appears to the right of the main keyboard. The NumLock key is used to switch from numbers to editing keys.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText130">16. The processor also is called the ………………………………. .</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText135">2. The ……………………. Is the component of the processor that directs and coordinates most of the operations in the computer.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText140">9. ROM chips called……………….., contain permanently written data, instructions, or information.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText145">51. A(n) …………………………… is an external device that provides connections to peripherals through ports built into the device.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText150">35. A(n) …………………………… is a part of motherboard and connects the processor to main memory.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText155">52.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText156">53.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText157">54.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText158">55.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText159">56.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText160">57.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText161">58.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText162">59.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText163">60.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText164">31. ……………. is mass-produced, copyrighted retail software that meets the need of a wide variety of users, not just a single user or company.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText169">40. ………………….. is a collection of individual programs available together as a unit.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText174">42. Some …………………….is considered system software because it works with hardware and transmission media.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText179">39. ……………….helps home and small business users create newsletters, brochures, advertisements, postcards, greeting cards, letterhead, business cards, banners, calendars, logos, and Web pages.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText184">46. ………………… software is available to the public at no cost.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText189">33. With ……………., you can view, organize, sort, catalog, print and share digital photos.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText194">34. A(n)………………… is an online area where users have written discussions.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText199">36. …………………… is the electronic equivalent of a user manual.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText204">15. ……………………allows a user to plan, schedule, track, and analyze the events, resources, and costs of a project.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText209">17. ………………… software provides a means for sharing, distributing, and searching through documents by converting them into a format that can be viewed by any user.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText214">18. Which is not Communication Software?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText219">24. Which is Business Software?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText224">25. The internet (often called simply \'the net\') is a global ………………….of interconnected computers.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText229">45. ADSL* is more commonly known as ……………………………………</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText234">48. Before you can connect to the internet for the first time, you have to __________ an account with an ISP.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText239">49. Looking at web pages can be called \'navigating the Web\' but is more commonly called ________.</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText244">43. Which can keep a public diary of your journey through South America?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText249">7. If you want to find out about the First World War, where should you find it?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText254">10. What is the Internet?</string>
    <string name="postUnit1to5styleText259">37. With …………………, users can view message detail such as the length of calls and, in some cases, read message contents instead of listening to them.</string>


    <!--pre unit1-5-->
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText1">Pre-test</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText2">Unit 1-5</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText3">Direction: Choose the best answer.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText4">1. Computer literacy, also known as digital literacy, involves having a current knowledge and understanding of……………………………….</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText5">a. computer programming</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText6">b. computer and their uses</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText7">c. computer repair</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText8">d. All of the above</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText9">2. ……………………. is/ are a collection of unprocessed items, which can include text, numbers, images, audio, and video.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText10">a. Program</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText11">b. Instruction</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText12">c. Data</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText13">d. Information</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText14">3. A ……………………….is a specific type of social networking Web site that allows users to cerate a online photo album and store and share their digital photos.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText15">a. blog</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText16">b. chat room</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText17">c. podcast</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText18">d. photo sharing community</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText19">4. A ………………. Is recorded audio stored on a Web site that can be downloaded to a computer or portable media player.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText20">a. podcast</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText21">b. social networking Web site</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText22">c. blog</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText23">d. speaker</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText24">5. …………………….. consists of the programs that control or maintain the operations of the computer and its devices.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText25">a. Application software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText26">b. A communications device</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText27">c. System software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText28">d. A graphical user interface</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText29">6. A (n) ……………….message is a real-time Internet communication, where you exchange messages with other connected users.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText30">a. text</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText31">b. instant</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText32">c. video</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText33">d. Picture</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText34">7. Many large companies use the word(s), …………………, to refer to the huge network of computers that meets their diverse computing needs.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText35">a. multimedia</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText36">b. telecommuting</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText37">c. enterprise computing</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText38">d. information technology</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText39">8. ………………is a system that attempts to imitate the behavior of the human brain.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText40">a. A neural network</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText41">b. E-commerce</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText42">c. A kiosk</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText43">d. Telemedicine</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText44">9. What is a computer?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText45">a. It’s an appliance device which can accept data in a certain form, process the data and give the results of the processing.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText46">b. It’s an electronic device which can accept data in a certain form, process the data and give the results of the processing.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText47">c. It’s a motorized device that processes output into input.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText48">d. It’s a storage device records writes and retrieves reads items to and from storage media.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText49">10. What does CPU stand for?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText50">a. Central Processing Unity</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText51">b. Central Processing United</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText52">c. Central Processing Unit</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText53">d. Central Programming Unit</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText54">11. An ……………………….device is any hardware component that allows you to enter data and instructions into a computer.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText55">a. input</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText56">b. output</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText57">c. electronic</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText58">d. external</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText59">12. Three commonly used ……………………………device are a printer, a monitor, and speakers.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText60">a. input</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText61">b. output</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText62">c. electronic</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText63">d. external</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText64">13. ………………………..is any electronic or mechanical part you can see or touch.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText65">a. Software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText66">b. Hardware</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText67">c. Storage device</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText68">d. Speaker</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText69">14. Which are the components of a computer?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText70">a. Input devices, Output devices, System unit, Storage devices and Communication devices.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText71">b. Input devices, Output devices, System unit, Storage devices and External devices.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText72">c. Input devices, Output devices, System unit, Storage devices and Control devices.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText73">d. Input devices, Output devices, Stem unit, Storage devices and Communication devices.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText74">15. Which are input devices?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText75">a. speakers, printers and monitor</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText76">b. card reader, USB flash drive and memory cards</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText77">c. microphone, modem and external hard disk</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText78">d. scanners, keyboards and mouse</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText79">16. Which is not an output device?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText80">a. A printer</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText81">b. A speaker</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText82">c. A Monitor</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText83">d. A Keyboard</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText84">17. Which is not a storage device?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText85">a. A memory card</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText86">b. A hard disk drive</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText87">c. A scanner</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText88">d. An external hard disk</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText89">18. What are the main parts of the CPU?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText90">a. Hardware and software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText91">b. Keyboard output devices</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText92">c. Storage devices</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText93">d. Hard disks</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText94">19. What does ALU stand for?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText95">a. Architecture Logic Unit</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText96">b. Arithmetic Logic Unit</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText97">c. Artificial Logic Unit</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText98">d. Arithmetic Login Unit</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText99">20. What does ALU do?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText100">a. To store information</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText101">b. To control data</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText102">c. To perform mathematical calculations</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText103">d. To feed information</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText104">21. What type of memory is temporary?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText105">a. RAM</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText106">b. ROM</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText107">c. Cards</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText108">d. BIOS</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText109">22. What type of memory is permanent and includes instructions needed by the CPU?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText110">23. If you want to change the capital letters permanently, what should you do?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText111">a. Press the caps lock key</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText112">b. Press the tab key</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText113">c. Press the alt key</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText114">d. Press the shift key</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText115">24. Scanners, printers and webcams are ……………………</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText116">a. extras</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText117">b. peripherals</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText118">c. externals</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText119">d. Internals</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText120">25. What do you call the mouse which doesn’t have a ball?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText121">a. An optical mouse</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText122">b. An option mouse</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText123">c. An alternative mouse</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText124">d. An alphabet mouse</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText125">26. ……………….. appears to the right of the main keyboard. The NumLock key is used to switch from numbers to editing keys.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText126">a. Cursor control key</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText127">b. Alphanumeric key</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText128">c. Function key</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText129">d. A numeric keypad</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText130">27. The processor also is called the ………………………………. .</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText131">a. chip</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText132">b. adapter card</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText133">c. central processing unit</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText134">d. motherboard</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText135">28. The ……………………. Is the component of the processor that directs and coordinates most of the operations in the computer.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText136">a. machine cycle</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText137">b. control unit</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText138">c. arithmetic logic unit</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText139">d. register</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText140">29. ROM chips called……………….., contain permanently written data, instructions, or information.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText141">a. memory cache</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText142">b. register</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText143">c. transistors</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText144">d. firmware</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText145">30. A(n) …………………………… is an external device that provides connections to peripherals through ports built into the device.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText146">a. expansion bus</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText147">b. port replicator</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText148">c. docking station</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText149">d. Synthesizer</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText150">31. A(n) …………………………… is a part of motherboard and connects the processor to main memory.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText151">a. front side bus</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText152">b. system clock</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText153">c. memory module</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText154">d. expansion bus</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText155">32.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText156">33.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText157">34.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText158">35.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText159">36.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText160">37.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText161">38.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText162">39.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText163">40.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText164">41. ……………. is mass-produced, copyrighted retail software that meets the need of a wide variety of users, not just a single user or company.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText165">a. Packaged software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText166">b. A Web application</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText167">c. Open source software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText168">d. Custom software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText169">42. ………………….. is a collection of individual programs available together as a unit.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText170">a. Shareware</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText171">b. A software suite</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText172">c. Packaged software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText173">d. Custom software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText174">43. Some …………………….is considered system software because it works with hardware and transmission media.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText175">a. communication software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText176">b. business software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText177">c. application software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText178">d. project management software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText179">44. ……………….helps home and small business users create newsletters, brochures, advertisements, postcards, greeting cards, letterhead, business cards, banners, calendars, logos, and Web pages.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText180">a. Note taking software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText181">b. Personal DTP software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText182">c. Blog ware</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText183">d. A personal information manager</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText184">45. ………………… software is available to the public at no cost.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText185">a. Packaged</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText186">b. Custom</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText187">c. Open source</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText188">d. Public-domain</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText189">46. With ……………., you can view, organize, sort, catalog, print and share digital photos.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText190">a. desktop publishing software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText191">b. clip art</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText192">c. Photo management software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText193">d. Spreadsheet software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText194">47. A(n)………………… is an online area where users have written discussions.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText195">a. FTP Program</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText196">b. Web browser</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText197">c. text message</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText198">d. Newsgroup/ message board</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText199">48. …………………… is the electronic equivalent of a user manual.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText200">a. Online Help</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText201">b. Web-based training</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText202">c. E-learning</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText203">d. Distance learning</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText204">49. ……………………allows a user to plan, schedule, track, and analyze the events, resources, and costs of a project.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText205">a. Document management software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText206">b. Accounting software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText207">c. Project management software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText208">d. CAD software</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText209">50. ………………… software provides a means for sharing, distributing, and searching through documents by converting them into a format that can be viewed by any user.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText210">a. Word processing</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText211">b. Document management</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText212">c. Portable Document Format (PDF)</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText213">d. Database</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText214">51. Which is not Communication Software?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText215">a. E-mail</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText216">b. Chat room</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText217">c. Newsgroup / Message Board</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText218">d. Web Page Authoring</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText219">52. Which is Business Software?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText220">a. Tax preparation</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText221">b. Video and Audio Editing (for Personal Use)</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText222">c. Data base</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText223">d. Blogging</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText224">53. The internet (often called simply \'the net\') is a global ………………….of interconnected computers.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText225">a. net</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText226">b. network</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText227">c. warming</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText228">d. Presenting</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText229">54. ADSL* is more commonly known as ……………………………………</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText230">a. longband</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText231">b. broadband</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText232">c. wideband</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText233">d. webband</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText234">55. Before you can connect to the internet for the first time, you have to __________ an account with an ISP.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText235">a. set</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText236">b. set up</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText237">c. set in</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText238">d. set out</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText239">56. Looking at web pages can be called \'navigating the Web\' but is more commonly called ________.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText240">a. \"surfing the net\"</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText241">b. \"skiing the net\"</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText242">c. \"swimming the net\"</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText243">d. \"searching the net\"</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText244">57. Which can keep a public diary of your journey through South America?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText245">a. Blog</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText246">b. Webmail</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText247">c. Online radio</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText248">d. Portal</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText249">58. If you want to find out about the First World War, where should you find it?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText250">a. instant massaging</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText251">b. online encyclopedia</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText252">c. portal</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText253">d. chatroom</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText254">59. What is the Internet?</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText255">a. A wireless fidelity network uses radio signals to provide high-speed.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText256">b. A wide-area network spanning the globe.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText257">c. A programs that help users establish a connection to another computer or network.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText258">d. A type of hardware capable of transmitting data, instructions, and information between a sending device and a receiving device.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText259">60. With …………………, users can view message detail such as the length of calls and, in some cases, read message contents instead of listening to them.</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText260">a. Web services</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText261">b. Internet telephony</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText262">c. Visual voice mail</string>
    <string name="preUnit1to5styleText263">d. Video messaging</string>



</resources>
